Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Yes, Mr. Burnish,
the venue
is completely sold out.
This is the most important
discovery of the century,
and everyone wants to see it.
Yes, the press will be there.
This is your big day,
Mr. Burnish.
You won't be disappointed. I promise.
Easy. Easy, boy.
Code Red!
Who left the enclosure open?
Stay back!
All right, move in slowly.
No sudden movements.
What's happening?
Oh!
- Whoa!
- Oh!
Um...
who's telling Mr. Burnish?
On your right.
- Hey, want to shoot some hoops?
- Maybe later.
- Number two, extra spicy.
- Xie xie.
Nah. Nah,
I'm going out with Peilin,
but, uh...
eh, maybe I'll stop by.
Aw, it would be
so fun if you could come.
Yi!
I'm leaving for work.
Yi?
Are you awake?
Bye, everybody.
Have a great day.
Eh. What are you
supposed to be?
A famous person now?
Uh, where are you going?
I've got stuff to do.
Stuff? What is this stuff?
It's summer holiday.
Either be busy,
or be on holiday.
That is what I say.
- Be careful out there.
- Of course.
Be back before dinner.
- I'll try.
- Warm enough?
- Toasty.
- No boys.
- What? No, no boys.
- Do you need any money?
Mom, Nai Nai,
I've got it covered.
Bye.
Okay. Bye.
What on earth do you think
she does all day?
Whoa! Sorry, sorry. Sorry.
- Heel.
- Hey!
- Would you guys give me a break?
Whoa, whoa!
Oh, my babies.
Money transfer?
Sorry. It's cash only.
We'll be back in a few hours.
- Hey, cutie.
- You're not my mom!
So, Jin, are you
going to Shuo's this weekend?
No. No, I'm heading to Beijing
to check out my school.
- I'm, uh, premed.
- Nice.
- Oh, med school?
- That's so hot.
I know, right?
Ugh. What's that...
smell?
She looks like she slept
in a dumpster.
Selfie!
He breaks left.
He breaks right.
He's going in for the dunk!
Whoa!
Hey, Yi.
Come shoot hoops with me.
Come on.
Sorry, Peng.
I don't have time.
Wh-Why don't you ask
the other kids?
The other kids are too little.
And some of them
are freakishly good.
Come on, Yi, you never play
with me anymore.
Peng, I've been busy all day.
Hey, hey, your cousin
will play with you.
Yeah, yeah,
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
Light show starts at 8:00.
Uh, buh-bye.
As usual, he's got a date.
Wait, wait. Yi, watch.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Stop and check.
Hey, Yi, you know
I can smell you
from all the way
over here, right?
Like you can talk.
I'm sorry, is there any
aftershave left,
or did you use
the whole bottle?
Why?
You hoping to borrow some?
- Oof, not sure it'll help.
- Very funny.
You guys want to work out some
of this tension on the court?
Forget it, Peng. We wouldn't
want to mess up Jin's hair.
And the new kicks.
No basketball for these babies.
Another time, okay, coz?
That's what you always say.
48 likes. Sweet!
Don't.
I know what you're thinking,
so just don't say it.
She's never at home anymore.
Ma.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Not another word.
So, that's it?
We're just going to
give up on her?
I'd never give up on Yi.
Look, we both know
what she's been going through.
She misses her dad.
We all do.
If we're patient and don't
push her, then just maybe...
Yi, is that you?
We've been waiting
for you to eat.
Oh, I-I ate on my way back,
so I'm good.
Either eat here or there,
but never on the move.
That is what I say.
Hey, Yi,
why don't we all sit down
together tonight as a family?
Family.
You need to eat.
You don't want to be
so short like your mother.
Oh, I'm-I'm okay.
Thank you, Nai Nai.
Yi, wait.
What would you say to playing
a little violin for us
after supper?
- Remember when you used to...
- I-I can't.
Can't? Why?
Uh, because I...
I-I sold it.
I, uh... I'm sorry.
No.
I will take this trip.
Someday.
Okay.
No, no, no, no.
Huh?
Hold up. Spotted something
at two o'clock.
There's nothing there.
Moving on.
Oh.
Hi, Mom.
Bye, Nai Nai.
Excuse me.
Bam! It came out of nowhere.
Then it was gone.
Did you see where it went?
Lady, I just told you.
It was gone.
What, uh... what was it anyway?
Um, let me take care
of the repairs to your truck.
A little compensation
for your silence.
It's a bribe.
Nai Nai, that's weird.
- Oh, so you're hungry now, hmm?
- Oh, yeah.
Starving.
Let them cool.
You'll burn your mouth.
I keep telling your mother
- you need to slow down.
- Ow! Ow!
- Spend more time here, at home with your family.
- Ow.
- Mrs. Lui called me today.
Says you're fixing
her computer.
And Mrs. Yuan in 4-B says
you're going to trim
her poodle's toenails.
I like that you're ambitious.
No one wants
a lazy granddaughter.
But, uh, busy, busy, busy.
What do you need to do
all that for?
I guess I just like being busy.
Yi.
Can we just talk
about this later, Nai Nai?
You don't have to worry.
You should listen to Nai Nai!
Hey, boy.
Or girl.
Are you hungry?
Whoa!
Hoo!
Yeah, you're definitely a boy.
Whoa.
I don't know
where you came from,
but you...
sure don't belong here.
You stay in here, okay?
There-there are people
looking for you.
Hmm.
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay. Okay.
No. Please don't cry.
Wait.
My dad used to play for me.
It always made me feel better.
All better, right?
Uh...
The...
Nah.
Good night, sleepyhead.
Wait.
Do you know that place?
Is that... is that your home?
You know, uh, um, home.
No way.
Okay.
Come on.
Creature from Mount Everest.
"Considered to be no more
than fairy tale and myth,
"enthusiasts still
hold out hope
that these creatures
actually do exist."
There's a yeti on my roof.
Captain, I am holding
you personally responsible
for that abominable
creature's escape.
Now, you will get every car
we have out there,
or I will send you back to
your job at the shopping mall.
Uh, yes, sir. Understood.
Attention, all units.
We need every car
out on the street.
I was dribbling,
and the guy was like, "Oh, no,"
and I was like, "Oh, yeah."
Want to play a game?
I can't.
Nai Nai will, though.
Hey, Nai Nai,
want to shoot some hoops?
You know I only play for money.
Uh, something's missing.
What in the...?
Peng, go get your cousin Jin
and see who stole
my air conditioner.
Go. Go, go, go, go.
Hey. Uh, what are you
doing out here?
Someone's gonna see you.
Where did you get that?
No, no, no, no, no.
Give it back now!
Do you hear me? Let go!
Peng, that does not make sense.
Why would they take it
to the roof?
Oh!
- Guys, what are you doing up here?
- Hey! Uh, hey!
- Get away from her!
- No. No, no, no, wait.
Okay, I'm calling the police.
Hello? Hello?
- No. Jin, don't.
- Yes, uh, there's a...
- there's a wild beast on our roof.
- Hang up, Jin.
- No, no. Stop, Jin.
- Yes. Um...
...a wild beast.
- Turn up that scanner.
- Yeah, yeah, on Heping Road.
- Please hurry.
- That's him.
That's the yeti.
Ring Mr. Burnish.
Jin, what have you done?
He's not dangerous.
Look at him. He's a yeti.
- Cool.
- What?
No, y-yetis don't exist.
Oh, no.
They're back!
You have to go.
Go. Run. Now.
Go.
Wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no.
No. No, no.
Wait.
Yi!
He stole Yi.
More like kidnapped.
Come on, Peng.
Yi!
We're never gonna
catch up to them.
Hey, Jin.
Hey, girls.
Whoo!
How many girlfriends
do you have?
Hurry!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa.
They're gaining on us.
Locked on target.
Dude, you darted Dave.
Uh, yeah, we lost them.
I want eyes on that target
at all times.
It cannot leave the city.
Watch out!
Hold on, Peng.
There! There they are.
Whoa!
I think we lost them.
Look, down there.
That boat's leaving the city.
You-you have to get on it.
Get into position.
- Oh, there she is!
- Oh, my gosh!
Take the shot.
What?
There's a girl with him?
Oh, no.
How is she gonna get away?
Wait, wait.
What time is it?
8:00. Why?
Time for the light show.
Ooh! Aah!
Come on, Yi.
Where are they?
They're gone.
Copy that. They're gone.
And I'm dead.
Don't rub it in.
Come on!
Keep searching!
Oh! There they are.
Come on, Peng.
Over there. That one.
You have to get on that boat.
When that boat lands,
don't stop.
Don't stop until
you reach your mountain.
Don't stop until you're home.
Okay? Home.
Oh, you-you have to go. Now!
Hide.
Yi!
Yi, are you okay?
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, Yi.
Don't you dare!
Yi!
I guess I'm coming with you,
huh... Everest?
Yi?
Yi, are you crazy?!
- Wait for me!
- Peng? Peng! No!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Peng!
I'm responsible for you.
Your mom's gonna kill me.
My babies.
No, no, no.
You think this is funny?
Do you even know
how much I paid for these?
What were you thinking, Yi?
You have gotten me
into so much trouble.
I am so mad at you right now.
You know what?
I-I can't even talk to you
right now! That's how mad I am!
The unveiling is
in one week, Captain.
Now, how am I supposed
to prove the yeti exists
when I don't have a yeti?
- Uh...
- No speaking!
Only leaving.
Dr. Zara,
what am I going to do?
The science community
will be there.
The press will be there.
The world will be there,
watching with their eyes.
Mr. Burnish, there are
many rare and exotic animals
you have collected
over the years.
These snakes, for example.
You're the only one
in the world
to have a newly born clutch
of rare whooping snakes.
Down, down, down!
Go in your hole,
you weird snakes.
Sir, please.
These creatures
are to be respected.
Hmm.
They would make a lovely belt.
Mr. Burnish,
they are one of a kind.
A one-of-a-kind whooping belt.
A belt that goes "whoop."
Do I want that?
I don't know.
Take them away.
Wait, how many snakes
are there supposed to be?
Uh, why?
We promised the public a yeti,
and nothing else will do.
Nothing!
I don't care if the yeti
is dead or alive.
I just need him.
Your gerbil is freaking me out.
Jerboa.
Duchess is an albino jerboa,
and she, too, is one of a kind.
Sir, as a zoologist,
it is my mission in life
to make sure that all animals
are protected,
especially the rare
and exotic ones.
That is the only reason
I agreed to find your yeti.
And you did.
For a few short days,
we had one,
but I cannot go
to that unveiling empty-handed.
I will not be made
into a laughingstock again.
Not, not, not, not, not!
Uh, there's news, Mr. Burnish.
News about you leaving?
A dockworker saw
a creature and some kids
boarding a cargo barge
last night.
Dr. Zara, you are the best
in your field.
Please, help me get him back.
Under one condition.
We bring the yeti back alive.
You have to promise me
he will not be harmed.
Fine.
Fine, fine, fine, fine, fine.
Captain, where did
that boat land?
Uh...
Yeah, Ma.
Uh, Beijing is, um... is great.
And the dorms...
the dorms are clean.
Peng? Oh, Peng is, uh...
Look at all those teeth.
Peng's fine.
Hey, hey.
Oh, and Yi came, too.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
She's, uh... she's checking out
the university.
Soda?
Oh, yeah!
Mom never lets me have any.
Catch!
Hey, Everest, come over here.
How long will we be here?
Oh, uh, excuse me.
Cafeteria food
is a little rich.
Well, I got to go, Ma. Bye.
I cannot believe that
you made me lie to my mother.
I love this stuff!
Hey, okay. Everest, look.
First, you go over
the Yellow Mountain.
Then to the Yangtze River.
And that river will take you
most of the way
to the Himalayas,
and finally to Mount Everest.
This is how
you're going to get home.
Whoa, wait.
Mount Everest?
No, no, no.
That has to be
hundreds of miles away.
Actually, it's thousands.
I just hope he can make it
all that way.
He, um... he seems capable.
Look at all those people.
- Hello!
- Peng, get down!
Ow!
Yeah, we should hide.
Wait. Why are we still moving?
Uh...
'cause we're not
at the dock anymore.
What?
No!
You know, I've never
been out of the city.
Wow. I can't believe
how beautiful
it is out here.
I can't believe
I haven't eaten in 24 hours.
I'm starving.
Uh-oh.
Guys, I got to go.
Just hold it.
Oh, no. He's got to go.
- Get me out of here!
- I can't.
Out of my way!
Got to go! Got to go!
My head.
- I'm good.
- Okay.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
One bar.
Okay, that's good enough.
- Good enough for what?
- To buy tickets home.
Okay, look, the next boat
leaves around 5:00,
so let's hope
that's enough time
to find our way back
to the dock.
Peng, come on. We're leaving.
Yes, waiter.
I'm ready to order.
I'll have some of Nai Nai's
pork buns with extra pork.
All right, get up, Peng.
We got to go.
And a side of pork.
Is he...
Why is he making that...
- Shh, shh, shh. Jin.
- Is he humming?
What's going on?
Whoa.
What is happening?
Whoa. Is that a...
A blueberry?
Food!
Guys, these are delicious.
That doesn't make any sense.
No, no, this is not possible.
It's not funny, all right?
This is cashmere!
Uh, Jin?
Now what?
Oh.
Everest, do something.
Run!
Incoming!
- Run!
- Go faster!
Oh, no!
Save yourselves!
I'm hit!
Tell Nai Nai's pork buns
I love them.
Hey, Jin, did you get
enough to eat?
Let's just say I've got
blueberries in places
where blueberries should never be.
Come on, Everest.
Okay.
Watch and learn.
Bank shot.
- I'm exhausted.
- What?
Why are you stopping?
Because, in about five minutes,
we won't be able to see
our hands
in front of our faces.
And that is exactly why
we've got to keep moving.
All right?
Come on, Peng.
We need to get back
to that dock.
First thing in the morning.
Yes!
There's so many.
- Bugs?
- Stars.
How come
they're only swarming me?
Maybe they're ladybugs.
Lady... Not funny.
Well, my mom told me
that the stars
are our ancestors
who always watch over us.
My mom says that, too.
My backpack?
Peng!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Great. No reception.
I'm entirely cut off
from my social life.
Mm. How traumatic.
Yeah, Yi, it is.
Because, unlike you,
I like having friends.
- I'm not some kind of a-a...
- Loner?
Is that what
you were gonna say?
Well, for your info,
I'm a self-proclaimed loner.
There's a difference, okay?
Fine, because in the morning,
Peng and I are headed back
to the city.
- I-I can't leave him.
- Yi.
You've seen what he can do.
He's-he's amazing.
He's... he's magical.
Oh, so now he's a magical yeti.
Do you realize
how crazy you sound?
Look what happened
with the blueberries.
That wasn't him.
That was a natural phenomenon.
Just one that
I can't explain yet.
One, two, three, four,
I declare a thumb war.
Go!
Hey, you cheated!
Will you two please
just give it a rest!
Oh, my gosh, I'm beginning
to sound like my parents.
That's it!
That's why
they get along so well.
Everest is just a kid.
He's probably, like, the same
age as Peng but in yeti years.
Stop hitting yourself.
Right. There's no way
that giant thing is a kid.
Wait. I'll prove it to you.
Everest, come over here.
This is you.
And your parents.
Aw. You have
your mother's eyes.
Don't worry.
I will make sure you get home.
What are you gonna do?
- Take him all the way back to Mount Everest?
- Maybe I am.
Jin, he needs to get back
to his family.
And what about your family?
Don't they need you, too?
Always busy, never home.
What's that all about, Yi?
Don't talk to me about family.
You have no idea.
No idea.
Your...
Your life is so easy, Jin.
Do you even... do you even
want to be a doctor,
or do you just think
that you'll...
I don't know...
you'll look good in white?
All right.
Call me shallow all you want.
At least I'm not delusional.
I don't care
if you think I'm crazy.
You're impossible.
Huh?
Is that Yi?
Wait. Don't stop.
It's really good.
Your nai nai said you stopped
playing after your dad died.
Peng!
It's okay, Jin. Really.
Was this your dad's violin?
Mm-hmm.
You know,
I really liked your dad.
Thanks, Peng.
Well, we better head out
if we're gonna
make it to the Yangtze River.
- You're coming?
- Yeah.
I checked,
and Dahe village has boats
leaving for the city
every hour.
Okay, well, when we get there,
you and Peng can take
a boat back, but...
I'm going to take Everest home.
Well, that boat
pulled in yesterday morning,
but we've unloaded all of the
cargo and didn't find anyone.
Would you mind
if we search it again?
- You got anything?
- No, Captain.
He was here?
Yes.
And it looks like
he fancies soda.
Stop!
Down there.
What was that?
Sorry, Doctor.
There's no sign
of them anywhere.
Sir, the yeti has disappeared.
It has been so long
since I've been out in nature.
- Sir, if we...
- Look at this tree.
It's a wonderful tree.
Look at the colors.
I love this tree.
You there, chop it down
- and put it in a bag, will you?
- Right away, sir.
I want it in my penthouse...
to be with me.
- Mr. Burnish.
- Right. What? What is it?
We should divide the team
and cover some ground.
Captain, let us fan out.
Yes, sir.
Now, on the map, that village
is only, like,
a centimeter away.
That can't be that far.
It must just be
on the other side of the...
The Yellow Mountain.
- Wow.
- Wait. Wait.
We are not going over that.
Come on, Everest.
I'll race you.
Hey, you guys,
wait right there.
Ooh. Everest, look.
Make a wish.
No, no.
They're for wishing.
Leg cramp. Stop for a sec.
Okay. I mean, if you
really need to.
I wish I was
a basketball superstar.
Starting
in the championship game,
the mighty Peng!
Wait, is that a drone?
Cool!
Uh, okay.
- Not so cool. Not so cool.
- Oh, no.
It's those guys from the city.
I told you
this was a crazy idea.
- Captain, I have footage.
- Copy that.
Those little thieves
stole my yeti.
- Get us there.
- Keep your eyes on 'em.
- We're on our way.
- Uh, what now?
I wish there was
a way out of here.
Uh, what's going on?
- Whoa!
- Yi, let go of that.
It's dangerous.
Everest, are you sure
about this?
No! Peng!
Get down from there right now!
Hey, Peng!
- Jin, jump!
- Jump!
No! Get down here!
Give me your hand!
Got you.
Meet me at that village
by the river!
- We'll be there!
- And take care of Peng!
Wow.
Whoo! Whoa!
Yeah!
- Whoa!
- Everyone, push!
Uh-oh.
- Whoa!
- Are you catching this?
- Is that a giant...
dandelion?
Giant dandelions?
Look, stop messing about
and get my yeti!
Uh, yes, sir.
Let's take 'em down.
Yeah!
Take that, drones.
So, who's going to tell
Mr. Burnish?
Not it!
- Help!
- Wait, where are we going?!
I hope you're not hurt.
Let me introduce myself.
- I'm Dr. Zara.
- I know who you are.
You do?
Yeah.
You're the bad guys.
Aah!
Your gerbil is freaking me out.
A boy that knows his gerbils.
I like him.
Bad? Listen,
you've got this all wrong.
That wild beast is
unpredictable, even dangerous.
We were trying
to rescue your friend
when the yeti kidnapped her.
He did kidnap her.
Listen, you twit!
I own that yeti.
He is my yeti.
I want my yeti back!
Right? Just nod.
Mr. Burnish, please.
Ow.
All right, look.
I-I just need to find my cousin
and my friend
and get 'em back
to the city in one piece.
I can get all of you
back to the city,
but the only way
I can help your friends
is if I know where they are.
Do you know?
That yeti is the pinnacle
of my research.
I really need him back.
I don't know where they are,
but I do know
where they will be.
Brace yourselves!
Everest.
No, over here.
That was amazing, Everest.
You saved us, and now we're...
we're... we...
Where are we?
All I know is
we're a long way from Jin.
Yeah, well, that's his fault.
He should have jumped.
I mean, why...
why doesn't he ever just jump?
He did. He jumped on that boat
back in the city.
That's what got him on
this trip in the first place.
Yeah, but that's because
he was worried about you.
You're his family.
Yi, he thinks of you
as family, too.
Wh-What?
Hey, little turtle.
Everest, Jin said Yi
was like his little sister
when they were kids.
She was always doing
something crazy
that would get her
into trouble,
so he had to watch out for her.
And he still does.
I... I-I think
we should get going.
But don't worry.
I can get us out of here.
Let's go.
Put 'em down, Everest.
Suddenly, I saw it.
A yeti. A real yeti.
Cold eyes staring.
It tried to kill me!
I needed to protect myself.
I swung my ice ax...
and it was gone.
No footprints.
Nothing.
I rushed back to tell the world
what had happened,
but without proof...
they laughed at me.
They laughed at me.
You spent all these years
trying to get your proof?
Mm-hmm.
I'm so used to
looking down on the world,
it's amazing
how small one feels
just by looking up.
Mr. Burnish, we need to get
an early start.
Thanks to Jin, we've learned
the yeti's whereabouts.
Yes, yes.
Duchess... is that your name?
You're kind of cute, you know,
in your own ugly,
beady-eyed kind of way.
I can't feel my feet.
"Don't worry.
I'll get us out of here."
What was I thinking?
We are completely lost.
Everest is
nowhere near his mountain,
and for all we know, Jin...
Jin could be in trouble
right now, and it's...
It's all my fault.
Jin said this trip was
a crazy idea, and...
I don't know, maybe...
maybe he's right.
I mean, but...
we could sure use him
right now.
Yeah.
And the map on his cell phone.
It's okay, Everest.
It's just a koi fish.
That's weird.
Why are they swimming
against the current?
They're actually trying
to get back home.
Ooh.
Yeah, let's just put him back.
Do you think he'll make it?
Well, he's sure gonna try.
You know these fish are
the symbol of perseverance?
What?
It's, uh... it's just
something my mom told me.
It means that,
when things get really tough...
...they never give up.
You know what, guys?
We have to keep going.
Come on.
Come on, you guys, let's go.
Everest, put the fish down.
Into the water.
- Ow.
- Get back, you abominable creature.
Back!
That's great. Of course.
He said in
the sweetest little voice,
"You're cute in your own ugly,
beady-eyed kind of way."
I tell you, he's going soft.
We need to act fast.
If that kid is right
and we find the yeti
at the river tomorrow,
use any means possible
to take him down.
I thought we had to keep
the yeti alive.
The buyer won't pay us
unless he's still breathing,
but if he's a little banged up,
who cares?
They're just gonna chop him up
into little pieces
for their experiments anyway.
Well, what do we do
with the kids?
If you want your ten percent,
you'll get rid of them...
for good!
Oh, and get rid of this rodent
I've been carrying around.
Do you know
how hard it is to keep up
this British animal-lover act?
I'm done!
Duchess? But she's
a one-of-a-kind albino jerboa.
She's just a rat, you idiot!
Hey. My keys.
Here. I think you're
better off with this guy.
Mmm. Not now.
All right, let's see.
SUV? Too loud.
Transporter? No.
What's this one?
Sweet.
Check the hair.
Looking good, Jin.
Thanks, Jin.
All right, let's do this.
Oh!
It's okay, babies.
It's okay. I got you.
Nope. Nope.
I can't do it.
All right, fine, just take it!
Be the koi fish.
That's it, Peng.
You keep swimming.
What was that?
Come on!
All right!
No more swimming!
Yeah, but how
are we gonna catch it?
Whoo-hoo!
Now, this is the way to travel.
Ready, Everest?
Again.
You know, Everest, I...
I can't figure you out.
I mean, how...
how do you do that?
Ah.
Maybe it's his gift,
like when you play the violin
or when I play basketball.
Everest talks to nature.
Now, that... that is a gift.
- Well, this is the village.
- Do you see Jin?
Through that mob?
Are you kidding me?
- We need to both look for him.
- What about Everest?
- Move it, yaks.
- Oh.
Got an idea.
Grab all of that rope.
Can you see anything?
Nope.
Yi, there he is!
Jin! Jin!
We're gonna lose him.
I'll run ahead.
Stay there and blend in.
Oh, your yak is odd-looking.
Hey, don't body-shame my yak.
Jin! Jin!
- Yes?
- Whoa.
I am so sorry.
No.
Keep looking.
He said they would be here.
I can't believe
he crashed my bike.
Look!
Target spotted.
Move out.
They found us. Let's go.
Go!
Go, Everest, go! Move it!
- No. Oh, no.
- Hey, you.
Need a ride?
Jin?
- You showed up.
- Of course I did.
Wait. Where's Peng?
Everest!
Oh, no.
Coming in at four-foot-ten
and ready to take the game,
the mighty Peng!
High five! Yeah!
- Everest! Peng!
- Peng, come on!
Jin, I knew you'd be here.
Good to see you, coz.
What happened to your babies?
Well, Peng...
my babies are all grown-up.
Hang on.
Captain, don't you dare
let them get away!
Hold on. This little lady has
a few tricks up her sleeve.
Go faster!
I'm trying!
Everest, do something.
- Hurry, Everest.
- Whoa.
- It's working.
- Uh...
Oh, no.
Guys? Guys!
- Turn! Turn, turn, turn!
- Turn! Turn!
Ow!
Whoa.
This is unbelievable.
Peng, Peng, look.
It's okay.
Wow!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
This is amazing!
This is impossible.
Come on, Everest.
Make it go bigger!
Ooh. Whoa!
Whoa!
Higher!
Okay. Okay, that's enough.
- Slow down!
- Peng!
Slow down!
- Where is he?
Peng?
Oh, no.
Everest, no. Everest.
Hold it in.
No, no!
Hey, Jin.
You got a little something
right here.
No.
Oh, no.
No. No.
Yi?
You okay?
Yeah, um...
that violin meant
everything to me.
When we were little,
you know my dad used to play
all the time.
Um...
but every night,
when he was tucking me in,
he would play this one song
just for me.
And...
I don't know, it-it made me
feel like everything...
was gonna be okay.
Yi, I'm sorry.
I'm-I'm sorry for what I said.
Too busy, never home. I...
No. No, no, no, you-you're...
you're right.
I... I know I keep busy.
I just... I don't know why.
I mean, I... I-I...
I miss him, and I don't want
to miss him, but...
I haven't even cried yet, Jin.
And my family,
we're all so distant, and I...
I don't know.
I don't... I-I...
I don't know what to do.
Well, are you sure they're
the ones who are distant?
But you were right
about me, too.
Yeah, hate to admit it,
but, I mean, that thought
about looking good
in the white doctor's coat,
it did cross my mind.
I am a horrible,
horrible person.
Yeah, you are the worst.
I really... I am.
Yi, listen.
If those people find Everest,
we're all in danger.
Wait, do... do they know
where I'm taking him?
They are headed
to the Himalayas, sir.
And the yeti's powers
will grow even stronger
the closer he gets
to those mountains.
But there's still one more
chance to capture your yeti.
At the foothills of those
mountains, there's a bridge.
Once the yeti crosses it,
he'll blend in, disappear.
We will never find him again.
I've never seen powers
like those before.
It's intimidating.
Stay the course, sir.
After this, no one will ever
laugh at you again.
You're right.
Captain, we are going to need
reinforcements.
Lots... of reinforcements.
Yes, sir.
What do those powers
mean for us?
That yeti's
price tag just doubled.
Hey, you guys,
did you find that thing?
We're working on it.
- There it is.
There it is.
Really, Dave?
Come on. Come quickly.
Everest?
You okay?
- Is that...
- Yeti hair?
Yep.
See?
It's as good as new.
No.
It's better than new.
Hey. When did you buy these?
Oh, I-I-I didn't buy them.
They were my dad's.
He kept postcards
of all the places
he wanted to take us someday.
The... the whole family.
Yi, they're all of the places
we've been.
What?
No way. What... How...
How is this possible?
That can't be.
We've been to all of these.
All but one.
The Leshan Buddha.
This is the place that my dad
wanted me to see the most.
This... this is incredible.
You brought me here,
didn't you?
Whoa.
Impossible.
Wow.
I wish Dad were here
to see this.
It's beautiful.
Thank you, Everest.
You did that, Yi. You did.
I did that?
Whoa.
Come on, Everest.
Yi.
We are so going
to the Himalayas.
Come on, you guys.
Whoa, whoa!
Okay, okay!
Hold on, Peng. Whoo-hoo!
Come on. If we keep going,
we'll get to the Himalayas
by morning.
Those guys are not gonna stop
until they get... Everest!
Is that better?
Maybe.
We still have to
keep going, though.
I know.
Will it be the same?
You know,
when Everest goes home?
With us, I mean.
Like, will you guys
still want to hang out?
Of course we will, Peng.
You know, I'll sure miss
seeing these stars.
Yeah, but even though
we can't see them,
we'll still know they're there.
So, that's kind of cool,
isn't it?
Yes, Peng, that's very cool.
It's not funny.
Loch Ness Monster?
Chupacabra?
I mean, what if they exist?
Oh, my gosh.
My whole life has been a lie.
Wow. The Himalayas.
- Whoa.
- Awesome!
Everest, look.
Just across that bridge
is home.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go, let's go!
Everest! Wait up!
Oh, no.
Go! Go back!
Whoa!
Go, go, go!
Everest, run!
Go to your mountain now,
before it's too late.
Captain, hurry.
Get my yeti! Get him now!
No, no, no, no, no, no,
you're going the wrong way!
He's on the move!
It's amazing.
Mr. Burnish,
we're missing our chance.
Load tranq guns.
Wait! Hold your fire!
Get back!
Mr. Burnish!
Take the shot!
Oh, no.
He's defending them.
Mr. Burnish.
Mr. Burnish!
Doctor, I was wrong.
You were right.
The yeti must be protected,
and the best way to protect
the yeti is to let him go.
We must let him go.
Captain, order your men
to stow their weapons.
Do it now!
Hmm.
Quick!
Mr. Burnish needs help.
Captain.
Fire at will.
- Fire!
- Fire! Fire!
Everest!
- No!
- Get the kids! Go!
- Everest!
- No! No!
- Stop! Stop!
- Everest!
I'll make sure the yeti's out.
No! No!
You are never going
to escape again.
Wait, wait, get her!
Stop it!
- Yi!
- No! No! No!
- Yi! No!
- Well, that's one down.
- Yi!
- All right, move out.
- Yes, sir.
Copy that. Moving out.
- Yes, Captain.
- Go back! No!
- Go back! Yi!
- Yi!
Stop the car!
It's Everest.
No, this can't be happening!
- Let's go! - Go, go!
- I'm out of here!
Sir. Sir, wake up.
Yi! You're okay.
Everest!
I thought we had
to keep the yeti alive.
Dead will have to do.
No!
Yes!
Uh...
No!
Everest?
You are by far the most
extraordinary creature
I have ever seen.
That is exactly why
the world...
must never know you exist.
They would not understand.
I didn't.
Now, can I please help you
get back to the city?
Thank you, but...
I promised
to take Everest home,
and he's not home yet.
You're going to take Everest
all the way to Everest?
That is impossible.
Sir, with all due respect,
when Yi sets her mind
on something,
nothing is impossible.
Yes.
It's cold.
But there is something
I have to insist
that I give you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- See you later.
Don't worry.
I'll be waiting right here.
They just wanted
our coats, Dave.
Guys, it sure is
a long way up there.
Everest?
- Cool!
- All right.
Bring it!
Wow.
Yeah!
Whoa!
Everest, it's your mountain.
What do we do now?
I don't know.
- Whoa.
His parents.
Wow.
They'd be so good
at basketball.
We're finally home, Everest.
Home.
I can't...
I can't believe
the journey's over.
You're right.
It's not over.
Thank you, Everest.
I'll never forget you, Everest!
Goodbye.
Bye. Thank you.
- Ma?
- Yi?
You're back.
How was the trip?
Aw.
Yi?
I missed you both so much.
It's good to have you back,
granddaughter.
Why don't you get that?
It's probably the boys.
Who is ready
for Nai Nai's pork buns?
Look what I found
on your doorstep.
- It's addressed to all of us.
- Shh!
Come over here.
For your next adventure.
Hey, kids, how was Beijing?
Peng!
Oh, it was, um, life-changing.
Wow. That's great.
Everybody, dig in.
Mmm. Wow.
You know, I totally see what
you mean about these pork buns.
Uh-huh.
There is no one in the world
who likes these pork buns
more than me.
Well... maybe one.
Who?
Who else like my buns?
- No laughing. I'm serious.
- Oh, Nai Nai.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org