Hello?
Hope. Hope Adler.
Who is this?
Alpine Lake.
It-it's a youth camp
in the mountains.
I, um...
I had these dreams.
Seven numbers.
No area code,
so this call is local.
You're here in Colorado, right?
The numbers were carved in ice.
Yes.
Who is this?
Who are you?
Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Got to get up, man.
Finn!
You're hurting him!
Finney!
Please, stop. Please.
You done yet?
Yes.
Stay the fuck away from me.
Anyone else?
Hey.
What the hell was that?
New kid.
Are you just beating up
new kids now?
He started it.
What was it this time?
Uh, the usual.
"Heard you were the badass
that wasted a serial killer.
You don't look so tough."
He didn't really say that.
Yeah, he actually did.
Did you have to go
so hard on him?
In a situation like that,
the more blood, the better--
for the crowd.
Proves a stronger point.
You've made that point
more than once,
so maybe--
and I'm just spitballing here--
maybe the point
you're actually making
is less "don't fuck with me"
and more "I'm the guy to beat."
Hey, Gwen, Finn.
Great fight, man.
Thanks, Ernesto.
-Hi, Ernie.
-So, uh, tonight,
uh, I'm going to go down
to the Civic Center
to wait in line
for Duran Duran tickets.
-Duran Duran tickets?
-He just said that.
Simon Le Bon is so choice.
A-Are you going, Gwen?
I wish.
Those tickets cost a mint.
My treat.
I was gonna buy two anyway.
It'd, you know, be cool
to have someone to go with
who's... who's also a fan.
-For real?
-For real.
That'd be radical.
Consider it done.
All right, well,
I-I got to get to shop class.
See ya.
You know that's a date.
-No, it's not.
-Yeah, it is.
Okay, so what if it's a date?
I don't know, I...
I just don't like him.
I don't get why.
He's really nice.
Besides that,
don't you think Robin
would want you looking out
for his kid brother?
But that doesn't mean letting
him boink my little sister.
-Ow.
-Don't be gross, jizz mopper.
Welcome back to Night Flight.
Here's German band FEX
with their new hit,
"Subways of Your Mind."
Night, son.
I'm off to bed.
Night.
Don't stay up too late.
Yeah, sure.
If you try to touch me,
I'll scratch your face.
This face?
Hey.
Still not my thing.
Don't tell Dad.
Fuck off, slap-dick.
I'm no narc.
You okay?
I'm fine.
No, I-I mean...
I don't want to talk about it.
It's okay
that you feel this way.
You don't know how I feel.
No, but...
I know, however you feel,
it's okay.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey.
Hey, Gwen.
Gwen, wake up. What are you...
Why are you so cold?
Finn?
It's okay.
You were sleepwalking again.
Jesus. Your skin is like ice.
I had a bad dream.
It's okay.
Just... go back to bed.
I-I said I had a bad dream.
I heard you.
Just go back to bed.
Hey, witch.
Hey, Gwen.
Hey, Ernie.
Check it out.
Oh, choice.
I can't believe it.
So, uh, you're into
a lot of that...
that woo-woo stuff, right?
What? You mean ghosts?
Spirits?
Glimpses of the world beyond?
-Yeah.
-Okay, then.
Yeah, I believe in
all that woo-woo stuff.
Cool.
Uh, I-I brought you
something else.
Ernesto, is this lotería?
Yeah.
My abuela sells them
in her shop,
and I thought they looked cool.
They're like tarot.
These are beautiful.
I mean, you can use them
like tarot.
If you have the sight,
they can show you things.
And you have that, right?
Have what?
Oh, I mean, like, you have...
you have dreams and stuff,
and they...
they show you things?
Where did you hear that?
My parents.
Back, you know,
they said that the police got
an anonymous call where...
where, um, Robin's body was.
But they say it was you.
That you dreamed it.
Or-or something.
I don't like talking about that.
Mm, why not?
'Cause it's weird.
I'm weird.
Maybe I like weird.
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
Hello?
Who's this?
Hope. Hope Adler.
Who is this?
My name is Gwen.
Where are you calling from?
Alpine Lake.
It-it's a youth camp
in the mountains.
How did you get this number?
I, um... I had these dreams.
Seven numbers.
No area code,
so this call is local.
You're here in Colorado, right?
Yes.
The numbers were carved in ice.
By boys.
Underwater.
Yes. Yes.
I had the same dreams,
but the boys carved letters.
Who is this?
Who are you?
My name is Gwen.
Hello?
I-I said my name is Gwen.
Hello? Can you hear me?
You shouldn't be here.
Hey.
Hey, Gwen.
Gwen.
Am I really here?
You're okay.
You were sleepwalking again.
You came here in your sleep.
I heard you leave,
and I followed you.
I feel like I'm crazy.
What the hell?
-Hey, hey. Look at me. Hey, hey.
-What the hell?!
You're okay,
you're okay, you're okay.
I-I was on the phone.
Finn.
I was talking to Mom.
It was just a dream.
N-No, it was...
a dream, yeah, but it was her.
She called me.
From a youth camp.
A youth camp?
She reached out to me
from there for a reason.
Come on.
Let's get you out of here.
-What's this?
-Camp Alpine Lake.
The camp Mom called from.
We have to go there.
Gwen, stop this.
It was just a dream.
About a real place.
A place I found.
It's why I had the dream.
It's a Christian youth camp
up near Silverthorne.
What's this?
They're accepting
applications for CITs
for middle school winter camp.
What's a CIT?
Counselor in training.
No...
I'm not going to be a counselor
for junior highers
at some weird Jesus camp
you dreamed about.
No, you're going to be
a counselor in training.
-No, I'm not.
-Come on.
Dad has been hounding you
to get a job,
and this is a job that pays.
And we can find out what Mom...
I said no.
What's going on in here?
Uh, Gwen wants us to get jobs
at some Christian winter camp.
Not Camp Alpine.
Hmm.
Your mother worked there.
Wh-When?
Uh, it was
long before I met her.
It closed in '58.
How'd you hear about this place?
Uh, um, I-I had...
Some kids at school.
Said it was a good way
to, uh, make some money.
Christian camp.
You guys, you know I don't...
much like any of that
religion stuff, you know?
It-it's just a job, Dad.
Mom worked there.
I'm not crazy.
I never said you were crazy.
Don't let me hear
you took that thing
any faster than 55.
Y-Yes, sir.
I would like my daughter back
unscathed.
-Do you understand?
-Yes, sir.
Do you say anything else?
Yes, sir.
Uh, uh, I-I mean...
I don't like the way
he looks at her.
Yeah. Me, neither.
Damn it. Wait.
"Wait," what?
Good.
Go look after your sister.
Do me a favor while I'm gone.
Yeah, anything, son.
Don't get drunk.
Hey, come on.
When are you gonna believe
I'm done with all of that?
In two weeks,
I get my three-year chip.
I'll have it when you get back.
See you in a few weeks.
Okay. Great.
Finally get some peace and quiet
around this place.
I can't see the road.
This isn't safe.
We could drive off a cliff
and not even see it.
Stop the car.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna run
in front of the car
so I can see the road.
Just follow me.
Follow me!
Mando!
I found your stray CITs.
Straight ahead about 20 yards.
Park anywhere.
Thank you.
You must be the Blakes.
Yeah, how'd you know?
Oh, they closed I-6
at Silverthorne.
You're the only ones
who didn't get the call in time.
I'm Armando.
Or just Mando, if you like.
Come on. Come with me.
Let's get you inside.
What about all the kids?
Aren't they supposed
to arrive tomorrow?
Camp's canceled.
They won't plow the roads
until the storm passes.
How many people made it here?
Just you three.
Support staff has only
been here a week,
but otherwise, you're it.
I'm sorry to say it,
but for now you're stuck here.
Come on, Gwen.
You're with me.
This is it.
Take any bunk you want.
Heaters are on,
so just give 'em a few minutes.
It will be toasty in no time,
all right?
Have a good night, kids.
Sweet dreams.
I got to sleep in here alone?
Afraid so.
State law requires
separate housing
for male and female minors.
I'd stay in here with you,
but I'm not a registered
counselor, so no can do.
But my cabin is just over there,
if you need anything.
Night.
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
Who is this?
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Hello, Finney.
Hell is not flames, Finney.
It's ice.
Nothing burns like the cold.
Gwen. Gwen!
Gwen, Gwen, Gwen!
Hey, Gwen, Gwen, look at me!
Hey, hey, look at me!
Wake up! Wake up!
Hey, hey.
What's happening to me?
Oh, God, I feel crazy.
You were dreaming. You're okay.
-You're okay.
-I feel crazy.
You're okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
Gwen.
I had a bad dream.
Okay. Y-You... you all right?
Here, uh... lie down.
Jesus...
please don't let me have
another dream tonight.
Please.
Hey.
Y-You okay?
Yeah.
Did I wake you?
No.
Was that for real?
What?
You talk to Jesus
just like that?
Yeah.
You think it's weird?
Uh, no. No, not-not at all.
I th... I think it's hot.
You think it's hot
that I talk to Jesus?
Yeah. I mean, it might even
be hotter if you called him
Jesús.
You know, my mom is
Catholic as hell.
She'd love me dating
somebody who prays.
We're dating?
Uh, um, I mean, I was...
I was just saying that...
I'm a good Christian girl?
Sure.
Why not?
My mom was Christian, too.
Dad didn't want us brought up
in the church, but...
I asked a lot of questions.
And when he wasn't around,
she answered.
Did she know
about your dream thing?
I got it from her.
It drove her crazy.
I'm scared the same thing
will happen to me.
It won't.
You're too strong for that.
You don't think I'm a freak?
What's wrong with being a freak?
I'm a freak like my mom.
Were you close to her?
Yeah.
I think about her every day.
I can still see her face
so clearly.
She was beautiful.
I think... you're beautiful.
What about me?
Do you think I'm beautiful?
Finn, you rotting shit stain.
Have you been listening
this whole time?
Well, I'm still right here,
so it's not like
I had any choice.
I-I thought he was asleep.
Told you Duran Duran is a date.
Ernesto, I need to talk
to Gwen alone.
If it's about last night,
he knows.
Knows what?
Why do you think he's here?
He came to help us investigate.
Wait, you told him
about your dreams?
Hmm. Yeah, Finn,
I know about her dreams.
And about the calls
that you get.
-Gwen.
-We can trust him.
Okay, but it wasn't
yours to tell.
Okay, I haven't told anyone.
Because you don't have
any friends.
I... I have friends.
Name one.
One you've brought home
to hang out.
One you've even mentioned
in a conversation at all.
Gwen, it wasn't yours to tell.
I have to tell somebody, Finn.
You never want to hear
about my dreams.
-That's not true.
-See this?
This happened last night
in my dream.
One of the kids grabbed me.
In... in your dream?
-Gwen, this is bad.
-Morning, campers!
Another glorious God-given day
here at Camp Alpine Lake.
Breakfast in the mess hall.
Come get some grub!
News reports say this is
the worst blizzard since '46.
Denver is shut down.
Best-case scenario is
two days, maybe three.
It could be longer.
You've met my niece Mustang.
She works the stables
and in the kitchen with me.
Mustang? Like the car?
Like the horse.
Uh, how many other people
are here?
Just Kenneth and Barbara,
who run the offices.
Rest of the support staff
got out
before they closed the roads.
So, how did everyone sleep?
-Fine.
I noticed you slept
with the boys.
I can lose my camp license
for that. Don't do it again.
Now, for the $64,000 question:
Why are you guys here?
To be camp CITs.
No, I...
I get that.
I mean, none of you
ever attended here as campers,
and none of you listed churches
on your applications,
so that means you didn't get
one of our flyers.
So, why are you here?
Huh?
Our mom went here.
Oh. Camper or counselor?
Counselor.
Her name was Hope Adler.
"Was"?
She died seven years ago.
Mm. I'm sorry.
Do you remember her?
A lot of kids come through here.
Do you know her camp name?
Support staff and counselors,
they get camp names.
It's easier for the campers
to remember who's who.
Starlight.
You're Starlight's kids?
You do remember her.
Very well.
Sh-She was a true light,
that one.
Um, I-I'm sorry you lost her.
May I ask how she passed?
She killed herself.
I-I... I'm so sorry.
Look, I...
I-I'm just glad
you guys found us.
After you eat,
you should call your families
and let 'em know you're okay.
There's a phone
in the camp offices.
Wait, what about
the outside pay phone?
That thing's deader than disco.
Hasn't worked in over a decade.
That dead pay phone rang
last night.
Did you answer it?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure it was him.
Him?
Like, "him" him?
Oh, my God.
What'd he say?
What'd he want?
-What?
-It's ringing again?
Go call Dad.
I'll meet you when I'm done.
You got something to say?
Then say it.
It's cold here.
Who is this?
I don't remember.
What happened to you?
We don't know.
You don't remember anything?
There's three of us.
Okay. Where are you?
It's cold here.
It's cold where?
And it's dark here.
Tell me where you are.
We don't know.
My name is Finn.
Help us, Finn.
You have to try
to remember something.
How did you die?
We don't remember.
We're scared, Finn.
I understand.
-Okay, what do you...
-We're not supposed to be here.
What do you mean?
This isn't where we belong.
We weren't supposed to be here.
Something bad happened to you?
Help us. Please help us.
Tell me.
Tell me how I can help.
Find us, Finn. Please, Finn.
-Help us! Please come find us!
-Come find us!
You have to come find us!
We don't want to be here!
Yeah,
we're snowed in here, as well.
You guys just hold tight.
I'm sure they'll have you
out of there in no time.
Love you, kid.
Bye.
Welcome back to KMGH News.
The blizzard brought
the entire area to a standstill
as heavy winds and drifts
made all the roads impassable.
So much so that police
in several cities issued curfews
against the vehicles
being on the road.
And the restrictions still stand
to those who violate
the order...
Yeah, Jake, hey.
Listen, I need to call in
that favor.
Has the company fleet
finished plowing the property?
Excuse me.
Do you have any literature
on the history of Alpine Lake?
Uh, we have a brochure.
Damn. Nothing more in-depth?
No, there is no published
history of Camp Alpine Lake.
We are a youth camp,
not a historical society.
Barbara, these are guests.
No, Kenneth,
this is the young lady
who decided
to sneak into the boys' cabin
last night.
So, what exactly
can we help you with, sweetie?
Look, we just want to know
about some kids
that may have been
killed here in the past.
You don't need to hear
anything about that.
We don't?
You don't.
Philippians 4:8 tells us
to think on things
that are lovely.
Philippians 4:8 also says
to think on things
that are true, just and honest,
right, Barb?
Barbara.
We don't know the specifics.
This is not some haunted tour
or ghost camp.
This is
a Christian organization.
We don't discuss
those kinds of things here.
But some fucked-up shit
did happen here, right?
Have you always had
such a filthy, vulgar mouth?
Have you always been
such a sanctimonious twat?
Hey, hey, I-I think
you two should leave now.
Let's go.
I'll pray for you.
Hello?
Who is this?
Hope.
Uh, Hope Adler.
Who is this?
I can't see you.
Where are you?
Alpine Lake.
It's a youth camp
in the mountains.
It's so dark.
How did you find me?
I had these dreams.
Seven numbers.
No area code,
so this call is local.
You're here in Colorado, right?
Where were the numbers?
The numbers were carved in ice.
The ice of a lake?
Yes. Yes.
It's so hard
to remember things here.
It's so cold and dark.
Who is this?
Who are you?
We don't remember.
Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me?
We're not supposed to be here.
Ernesto!
Wake up!
You don't
have to answer it, man.
Yes, I do.
You have one job:
look after my sister.
I promise.
Hello, Finney.
What do you want?
It took me a long time,
but now I remember.
You're dead.
Oh, Finney.
You of all people know
that "dead" is just a word.
Tell me why you're here.
Why do you think I'm here?
'Cause you knew we'd be trapped.
Gwen?
Gwen! Gwen!
Did you think
that our story was over, Finney?
Did you really believe
you could do what you did to me
and that would be the end of it?
I'm not afraid of you.
And why should you be?
You killed me.
You won.
Tell me what you want.
What I have always
wanted with you.
What?
You want to scare me?
You know as well as I do
that fear is just the warm-up.
Gwen!
-Gwen!
-Hey!
Hey! What are you doing?
It's 3:00 in the morning.
G-Gwen isn't in her dorm.
I don't know where she is.
Have you guessed what it is yet?
What it is that I want from you?
"Want" isn't even
the right word.
It's more of an insatiable need.
So, have you got it yet?
No?
Fine.
I'll just tell you, Finney.
What I want is this.
I want to hurt you
in ways that
you can't even imagine.
You will pay
for what you did to me.
You made me kill my brother,
the person on earth
that I loved the most!
And then you killed me!
So now I am
going to destroy you, Finney...
...by destroying
the thing you love most.
Vengeance is mine.
Gwen! Gwen!
Gwen!
Help me!
Hey. Hey. Hey, Gwen.
Gwen, wake up. Gwen, wake up.
Gwen, are you awake?
Hey.
You awake?
You got the devil in you, child.
I've been on this earth
a lot of years.
Seen a lot of things
I can't explain.
But I've never heard of anyone
who got dreams
like the ones you describe.
Where do you think
they come from?
She's possessed.
My God, Mando, isn't it obvious?
I'm not possessed,
you judgmental cunt wagon.
You think this is funny,
Mustang?
You getting your horns clipped?
Yeah, I do.
Why don't you mind
your own business?
Why don't you stop acting like
this is the first creepy shit
you've seen up here?
Stop it.
Every single one of us
has seen or heard things
around here.
-You especially, Barb.
-Barbara.
Shut up, both of you.
Gwen, your dreams,
are you saying
they tell you the future?
Sometimes.
Other times, it's the dead
showing me things from the past.
What kind of things?
Like the smallest missing boy.
Felix?
He was running for his life,
wearing a yellow down parka.
A-And the tallest kid,
he wore a white parka.
Spike.
And scratched letters
into the ice above him: "WBH."
I think his head was cut in half
on the tree stump in the woods.
Lord in heaven.
The third boy wore
a denim jacket.
He was all burnt up,
like he'd been cooked
inside an oven.
-How'd you know that?
-Mando.
No.
Gwen, ignore everyone else
in the room.
It's just you and me right now.
The boy who was burnt up,
how did you hear about that?
I just told you.
He came to me in my dream.
He wants me to find him.
They all do.
They can't rest
until they're found.
-Whoa. You okay there, Mando?
-Mando?
Burnt pieces of
Calvin O'Keefe's denim jacket
were found by police.
Only they had that detail.
The police,
the former camp owner and me.
What about
what we saw in the kitchen?
That was no dream.
Have you heard of The Grabber?
Yeah. Who hasn't?
He killed a bunch of kids,
and then...
got killed when one escaped.
Yeah, h-his name was
Finney something.
Finney Blake.
Finn Blake?
Holy shit.
Gwen, when did all this start?
Weeks ago, when my mom called me
from this camp in a dream.
She wanted me to come here.
Wh-What does this have to do
with The Grabber?
It wasn't the devil
attacking me in the kitchen.
It was him.
I could see him. He's here.
This is from the last year
of camp before we closed down.
I-I was just the camp cook
back then.
There's me,
and there's your mom.
After Harlan, the owner,
closed this place,
I kept coming up here anyway,
hiking the area,
looking for those kids.
Then, when Harlan passed,
I bought this place
in an estate sale for a song
and reopened it.
I promised their parents
I wouldn't stop looking
until I found them.
So, every day,
weather permitting,
I'm still out
walking the trails,
digging up every mound of dirt.
Not a single morning goes by
that I don't pray for help
to find those boys.
I didn't know it was you
he'd send.
But now that you're here,
I'm not gonna pass up a chance
to put those kids to rest
once and for all,
for-for-for them,
for their families and for me.
No fucking way.
What is it with this family?
It's him. It's The Grabber.
-Are you sure?
-I know him,
and I know his face.
That's Bill.
Wild Bill.
He worked maintenance.
We called him Wild Bill
because he wore this
brown leather tool belt
loose around his waist
like a gunslinger,
and he got long, wavy hair
like Wild Bill Hickok.
Wild Bill Hickok.
"WBH."
This is where he started.
These boys were his first kills.
And Wild Bill became
The Grabber.
Mando, when did weird things
start happening around here?
Mm, not until a few years ago.
1978?
Sounds about right.
That's the year I killed him.
And his spirit was set free
to come back here.
Okay, but why would he do that?
Maybe his spirit draws power
from the fear of his victims
because their spirits
are not at rest.
How do we find these boys?
Their bodies are underwater,
in a frozen lake, I think.
But didn't the police search
the local lakes?
No. Why would they?
The lakes were frozen over
when the boys went missing.
Lake Maru is where
we take campers ice fishing,
so we store our equipment there.
Wild Bill used it
for the kids' hockey games.
He was a good skater.
That's the only lake
where he would have the tools
to make a hole in the ice and...
dump the bodies.
Okay, so i-if we find Felix,
Cal and Spike,
allow them to rest, as you say,
that would get rid
of The Grabber's power?
I think so. Yeah.
Okay, then.
At dawn, we head to Lake Maru
and look for those boys.
Very funny, Mustang.
Look what you made me do.
You made me kill my brother.
I know you're out there, Bill.
You can't have those boys
forever.
My name's not Bill.
Wild Bill, Grabber.
Evil is evil.
I want
to hurt you.
We are gonna get
those boys back, Bill.
My name's not Bill!
The devil's lettuce
is not allowed
in Camp Alpine property.
So fire me.
You've really been through it,
haven't you, kid?
There's... there's a certain
look in a young man's eye.
Kind of, um, quiet fury,
kind of...
deep rage when he's seen
too much or done too much.
Get in many fights, Finn?
So?
So, here's what I know.
Behind that kind of anger
is fear.
I'm not afraid of anything.
I know one thing
you're afraid of.
Yeah? What's that?
That you can't protect
your sister.
When I was on the streets,
I chose the wrong path.
Instead of facing my fears,
I chose anger.
You're doing the same.
I can see it.
Finn, son...
this is what I do for a living.
I meet half a dozen kids
like you every year.
Kids who are told
this is who they have to be.
You are stronger than you think.
You were strong enough
to kill The Grabber,
and you are strong enough to
let what happened with him go.
I don't know how to do that.
You got to...
face your feelings.
You can't just hold them in
and numb it all out.
You got to face it,
and then you can let it go.
He wants to kill Gwen,
to hurt me.
Oh, we're not gonna
let that happen.
I'm taking this with me.
Come on, man. I need that.
I'm doing you a favor.
This ain't even good shit.
We head to the lake
in an hour, at sunup.
Be ready.
Me and Ernesto are gonna
take shifts watching you, so...
if you have another nightmare,
we'll wake you.
What if you can't?
Then fight back.
I mean, it's your dream,
isn't it?
He makes it more than that.
What about those books
you read about dreaming?
You know, there's got to be
something you can try.
He's too strong.
I thought that once, too.
She's out.
Can I ask you a question?
Did you really talk to my
brother down in that basement?
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
Wh-What'd he say?
He said that your dad didn't
come back from Vietnam
because he couldn't leave
his buddies behind.
And that he wasn't gonna
leave me behind.
Yeah?
Yeah, that...
that was Robin all right.
Do you think he's still here?
I-I don't really know
what's on the other side,
but there's something.
And I hope it's good.
And I hope he's there.
But if he isn't,
it's not me
he's here looking after.
Wake me in four hours.
Wild Bill.
Nope, nope, no, no.
Y-You're staying in bed tonight.
You look like your mother.
Why is she in here?
A kindness, really.
To you, I mean.
A kindness to you.
A kindness?
It's what I can manage.
My mom dreamed about
Billy Showalter,
the paperboy.
He was the first kid taken
in our area.
She figured out you took him,
didn't she?
Isn't that obvious?
The kindness here
is me showing you the truth
before I do what I have to do.
Abandon all hope,
ye who enter here.
She didn't kill herself.
You killed her!
No. No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No, no.
No!
What did you do?
What have I done? What have...
No, no!
This is different than a dream.
I conjured this from my hate
and from whatever memories
hell let me keep.
Hell is different
than you think.
They take the best parts of you,
the human parts,
and leave only the worst bits,
only the sins.
I am a bottomless pit of sin.
What do you think happens
when you die in this realm?
I'd wake up.
Maybe.
Or perhaps...
you just die.
It's time to find out.
Hello?
You have to hide.
Gwen! Gwen!
Wake up!
Gwen!
Gwen, wake up!
Finn! Mustang!
Gwen.
What's wrong with her?
Gwen. Gwen!
Gwen!
-Gwen, wake up!
-Gwen!
-Gwen? Gwen, wake up.
-Gwen, wake up.
-Gwen!
-Gwen, wake up!
Gwen, wake up!
-Gwen!
-Hey!
Ah, naughty girl, Gwen.
Fuck you with a dinosaur dick.
Oh, salty tongue
for a girl so young.
What are you doing?
If someone tries to take
what power I do have
away from me,
I have every right
to defend myself.
Mando.
Tell the boys I miss them.
Mando!
Gwen, wake up!
-Gwen!
-Keep pressure on it.
Got it.
All right,
help me flip her over.
Gwen.
Gwen, wake up. Gwen?
-Gwen?
-Okay.
Gwen, can you hear us?
Gwen, wake up.
-Gwen, wake up! -Hey,
keep pressure on the wound.
-Got it.
-Gwen? Gwen, can you hear me?
-Is she breathing?
-Gwen, come on.
-You've got to wake up, Gwen.
-Come on. We need help.
Gwen, Gwen, if you can hear me,
you have to fight back!
Gwen, fight back!
You didn't bring me here.
I brought myself.
I chose to come here,
and I can leave when I want.
I understand now.
In a dream, I have power, too.
So?
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm fighting back, you grievous,
festering ass wound.
See you later, Wild Bill.
Mando.
Mando!
Is he dead?
I found... I found Felix.
I found him. I found Felix.
Mustang?
-What time is it?
-About 4:30.
What's happened?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Mando fell through the ice
on Lake Maru.
Oh, no.
He's okay, but he found one of
the missing boys in the water.
We're all gonna start looking
for the other two at dawn.
We need your help.
Not with that demon child
out there.
Her name is Gwen,
and she is the reason
we got to Mando in time.
That demon child,
she saved his life.
-I-I don't know, Mustang. We...
-You know what?
You want to be all
yellow-bellied and barn-sour,
lock yourself in this room
until it's safe,
you go right ahead.
But that ain't no kind
of true Christian behavior.
Sun's up at 7:00.
Gwen!
There you are. You okay?
Dad?
Hey, kids.
What are you doing here?
Heard you were snowed in,
so I called in a favor.
Oh, thank God.
We can finally get you
the hell out of here.
We have to stay.
-What?
Wh-What's going on?
Our work here isn't done.
He's after her, Dad.
He's... Who-who's "he?"
Him.
I don't know...
Gwen, um...
-Is this more dream stuff?
-Dad, don't.
Okay, we're getting out of here.
-Come on. Let's go.
-I'll get my stuff.
I'm not going anywhere.
Gwen.
He's going to kill you.
Okay, and I can't stop him.
But we have a chance.
A chance to protect you,
to keep you safe.
You're gonna take care
of me, Finn?
You can't even take care
of yourself.
You are just like fucking Dad,
putting your head in the sand
and numbing yourself
into oblivion.
Whoa.
Where did that come from?
You've seen
what he's been doing.
You're just ignoring it,
pretending you don't
smell it on him, in his room,
-in the backyard.
-Narc.
You can't narc about
what everyone already knows,
dingus.
You're just smoking your
fucking life away to pretend
-none of this happened.
-Shut up.
Well, it happened, Finn.
-And it happened to those kids.
-Shut up.
-And it's happening now.
And you two just want to run
and hide like you always do.
-Shut up.
-Bottle, joint.
-Same fucking Friday night.
-Shut up!
-Anything to stop the pain.
Anything to feel for a few hours
like what happened to you
down in that basement
wasn't real!
Shut up!
All right, you don't think
I don't know it was real?
You think I don't fucking know
it was real?
It's all I ever think about.
All right, you don't...
you don't know
what it was like down there.
Nobody fucking knows.
All right, I was...
I was so fucking scared.
God, I don't want to be
angry anymore.
I don't want to be
afraid anymore.
Hey.
You're the bravest person
I know.
Okay.
Gwen, look at me, please.
I know you want to stay.
I know, but if you really are
in danger here,
we need to leave right now.
No.
Sweetheart, I'm sorry,
but I'm not asking.
What are you gonna do, Dad?
You gonna beat me?
Take off your belt
and whip me into the truck?
Don't, don't...
Go ahead and try.
See if it works.
Your mother, right there.
There's your mother.
You're just like your mother.
Stubborn! You're so stubborn
right to the end,
even in the face of reality.
The end? The end?
Let me tell you
about the end, Dad.
Mom didn't kill herself.
Okay. That's it.
Let's all get
in the goddamn truck.
No, no, wait, Gwen.
What are you talking about?
Mom's dreams.
She was dreaming about
a missing kid, wasn't she?
Talking about camp
before she died.
That's why you remembered
the camp.
Yeah, but... Yeah, so? So?
She found him
long before he took Finn,
and he saw her,
and he came to our house.
No.
Holy shit.
He showed me that he killed her.
Dad, what was the first thing
you said when you saw Mom?
What?
You asked her,
"What did you do?
What did you do?"
And you blamed yourself.
You said, "What have I done?"
We were asleep when it happened,
when you found her.
How else could I know
what you said?
It wasn't your fault, Dad.
Oh, my God.
And it wasn't hers.
The man who took Finn
took her away from us
because she was onto him.
Because her dreams
weren't just dreams.
And neither are mine.
All right, pass me the cable.
Hey, Jesus.
I'm not doing so well.
I need help.
Some real fucking help.
We got to find
those other two boys
to take away his power.
I'm scared he's gonna kill me.
For real this time.
Please don't let that happen.
Get us out of here alive.
Don't let him win.
We're pretty much out of light.
Maybe Spike and Cal
are down too deep.
I was thinking the same thing.
We should've seen 'em by now.
Hey, whoa, girl.
You've done enough for today.
Oh, no, Gwen.
Gwen!
Gwen, wake up.
Need some help!
Hey, Gwen.
Gwen, wake up.
Sh-She accidentally fell asleep.
Accidentally, my ass.
He's here.
Oh, my God. Ken, Barbara!
He's still here. Keep looking.
Where is he? Where did he go?
The ice is breaking!
The cable!
Finn!
Whoa!
How the tables have turned.
Ernesto, get her out of here.
I remember the feeling.
Breathless, scared,
the whole of the world
starting to fade away.
I've got Gwen.
Watch out. I'm coming through.
-You all right?
-Here. Here.
-You got him?
-Yeah. I got him.
"O grave, where is thy victory?
O death, where is thy sting?"
Scripture?
God's not here.
You're alone.
No.
I brought friends.
The boys are found.
You're powerless.
Oh, you're so fucked.
Hell isn't flames, Bill.
It's ice.
You don't scare me.
Hey.
You okay?
You did good, Dad.
It's over.
He's gone.
Where'd he go?
The boys took him back
to where he belongs.
Hi. This is Armando Reyes
from Alpine Lake.
Yeah.
Good, good. Yeah.
I know it's-it's been a minute.
The reason why I'm calling is
I have some news about Calvin.
Yes.
Yeah, we finally found him.
What?
You can't hear that?
-Uh-uh.
-The phone is ringing.
Must be for you, then.
Hello?
Hi, sweetie.
-Mom?
-Mm-hmm. Yeah, baby.
I don't have much time,
but it's me.
Where are you?
You know where.
It's beautiful here.
-It is?
-Mm.
Yeah, so beautiful.
Just like you.
I... I miss you, Mom.
Oh. I miss you, too, sweetie.
But you did so well.
You saved those boys.
-I didn't save anyone.
-Yes, you did.
You set them free.
They're here
where they belong now.
Wait.
I have to ask you something.
Ask me anything.
Will I always be this cursed?
Oh.
It's not a curse, baby.
It was never a curse.
I have to go.
Tell your brother I love him
and that Robin says hi.
Kids!
Time to go.
Get a move on.
So, what do you think
of that Ernesto boy?
She could do a lot worse.
-How about you?
-No, Dad...
That Mustang girl
seemed pretty cute to me.
Ah. Dad, please just...
just drive.
Just saying.
Eyes on the road.
All right, I'm just saying.