[GAGGARA JINGLES]
♪ ♪
Why did Appayya (Father)
vanish right in this spot?
This is our place of origin, dear.
Our ancestors lived here.
It's a legend.
[OFFICER] Send a
share to the office, okay?
Kamala...
What's happening?
Move aside!
[GUN FIRES IN THE AIR]
- Scoundrel!
- Hey, Rampa!
What are you staring at?
My Grandpa's gun.
It fires at its will.
Continue the story.
Damn her punch landed well.
What do you mean by a legend?
Eons ago, Eshwara's
Ganas roamed this land.
Who are Ganas?
The Daivas we believe in.
A force that has become one with nature.
Whenever mankind strays
into Adharma (unrighteousness).
From the divine realm,
Lord Eshwara sends
his Ganas to protect
Dharma (righteousness).
Among those who came, was
the one we follow - Panjurli.
But to drink the blood of those on the
path of Adharma came another Daiva.
The fierce force, Guliga.
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
All of these Ganas came
to dwell in this sacred land.
Thousands of years ago, it was known as
KANTARA - A LEGEND
CHAPTER 1
It was the era of the Kadambas
who ruled over Banavasi.
The Palegaras of the west stationed by the
sea, served as the Kadambas’ vassal kings.
With the strength of his sword
a man shed a river of blood and
became the king of the vassals.
A monster in human guise.
Vijayendra of Bangra.
Unaware of the outside world,
our elders lived a peaceful life.
Among them was Baidi,
a little girl with dreams.
Jabbanna, look here.
Looks beautiful, right?
Did we just find a sacred stone?
Our people, who worshipped nature,
stood there seeing the Daiva in the stone.
Blood ran through the shallow waters.
One man stood
watching it all from afar.
Maayakaara
[BAIDI WAILING]
JABBANNA!
Our strong ancestors ended up
as slaves to Bangra's kingdom.
[WHIP CRACKS]
[LEVER CLANKS]
[MAN SCREAMS IN AGONY]
Gosh! Jabba!
One day, when the King
was taking a bath in the ocean.
Maayakaara was sitting
far away, dropping a hook.
[SWORD CLANGS]
Hey! His blood
shouldn't touch the water!
Seeing the spices, the king's eyes lit up.
Though it lacked the shine of silver or
gold, it was the foundation of their trade.
Where did you find this?
Lord Eshwara's garden of bloom
Kantara.
The king had everything.
Except for Kantara.
We're on the right path, right?
[FOREST AMBIENT NOISES]
- Where did the old man go?!
- He was right here!
The king had fallen into the
Maayakaara's magical trap.
[EERIE NOISE]
[HORSE PANICS AND NEIGHS]
He took in everything
the light revealed.
Lord Eshwara's garden of bloom
But it wasn't just light.
[WILD OXEN CHARGE FURIOUSLY]
[TREE BRANCH SNAPS]
Appa (Father)! It's burning!
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
Wait right here!
[EERIE NOISE]
[EERIE NOISE AT A DISTANCE]
[VIJAYENDRA SCREAMS]
Appa!
[TREE CRACKLING IN FLAMES]
What happened to the tree?!
Well, there goes the king of Bangra!
Huh?!
[GASP IN UNISON]
[GOES INTO TRANCE]
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
Swami Panjurli is here.
[IN TULU] If anyone steps onto the land of
sacred stone with destruction in their heart
Their blood shall be cleansed
only when it spills on this sacred soil!
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
Let my voice, which has
crossed lands in the air
Let it deliver this
message to all who hear it
And let it leave their ears trembling!
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
Rajashekhara, who ran into the forest in
a frenzy, headed straight toward Kadapa.
While some found
peace through worship
Others were out there, seeking
power through summoning.
From the story Rajashekhara
told about the sacred stones,
the Kadapa people set their
eyes on Kantara's powers.
With the help of the Kadapa tribe,
Rajashekhara returned to his kingdom.
Thus, darkness and
hideousness became one.
Decades passed, yet the fear of
Kantara lived on in Rajashekhara’s heart.
Whenever the land of Dharma grows parched,
the Ullaaya (Almighty) brings rain.
Thus, divine forces are born
in this soil, again and again.
[BABY COOING]
Jabbanna, look here!
There's a baby in the well!
Baidi chose to take in
the child nobody wanted.
Found at the Daivas'
origin, he was named...
Berme.
Back in Bangra, Rajashekhara
fathered two children.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYS]
But when he learned that the girl child
had no strength in her arms or legs...
[BABY COOS]
Why is this known as
Eshwara's garden of bloom?
When our beloved Lord Shiva
came here to perform his penance
Goddess Parvathi created this
garden so he could meditate in peace.
Who is Berme talking to?
Has he lost it?
You picked an abandoned infant
and are asking me if it's sane?
What can I do?
Come. Let's go.
As he grew up, Berme was
in awe of the sacred stones.
You should never step
into Kantara, my children.
But why?
There lives a Brahma-rakshasa.
[BOY LAUGHS]
What are you sniggering about?
Don't laugh.
There lives a Brahma-rakshasa!
Years passed and our ancestors,
who used the forest’s resources to live
left a share for the Daivas
and kept another for themselves.
The third share was left
at the edge of the forest.
They were made to believe that the
Brahma-Rakshasa would take that share.
For Kantara and
Bangra's next generation,
the fear of the Brahma-Rakshasa
became the boundary.
[EERIE NOISE]
As he aged, Rajashekhara
crowned his son King.
[CELEBRATORY TRADITIONAL MUSIC]
The King of the kings.
The Regal Emperor.
The Supreme Ruler of the People.
The Lord of Bangra.
The redeemer of Sri Rajashekhara's lineage.
The new ruler of the Bangra throne.
His Holiness King Kulashekhara.
All hail! All hail! All hail!
[CEREMONIAL HORN RESONATES]
Kanakavathi, let's go.
Kulashekhara, bow down to
the Rajaguru (The Royal Guru)!
My my! The priest's here!
Namaskara (Greetings)!
May God bless you!
Which God?
All you need are my blessings.
Wishing you well. Carry on.
A gift from the
Kadambas to the King.
My King! Whoa!
Can I take a look?
- It's shining, right?
- Look how awesome it is!
- My King!
- So heavy!
When the kingdom was
prospering under your rule
Was it truly necessary
to crown your son?
My father never got to
see me ascend the throne.
What I couldn't do for my father
I believe my son will achieve.
Will he really be able to?
I'm with him, aren't I?
As King, you made me
your minister, Kulashekhara.
We must find a
way to celebrate this.
Celebrate how?
Wars ended during my father's reign.
[GUNANANDA] You still
need to rule, don't you?
Well, you're right.
Shall we kick things
off with a hunt?
That's like it.
Where do we go?
Kantara.
What a scary forest!
Is there really a
Brahma-rakshasa in this forest?
Didn’t your father claim
he saw it with his own eyes?
Ah! Even if it's here,
what does it matter?
The men up ahead will
run into it before we do.
[BHOGENDRA CACKLES]
No matter who gets
caught, I hope I don't.
- AY BHOGENDRA!
- Yeah?
Ride the chariot slowly!
You're making me throw
up everything I drank!
I can't go any slower than this.
If it's that much trouble,
walk with the soldiers.
What?!
Can't tell who's king
or minister anymore.
- Give me an arrow.
- Take this.
- Give me the bow.
- Oh!
I forgot the bow.
Goddammit! This chimp brain!
Shows up for a hunt
with arrows and no bow.
What do I shoot this
with now, dumbo?
Sire! Excuse me?
Please tell the King to keep it low.
Give me the bow, moron!
Annu, somebody's
definitely there.
What happened?
Something flew by me.
Man has zero survival instincts!
Hey! Keep an eye out!
- Langur! Langur!
- Where?!
[LANGUR SCREAMS IN PAIN]
Bravo Madhukara!
That was a damn good shot!
- Of course. I showed him.
- Really?
- Bring the prey!
- Guards in the front, go on!
If you hear anything
inside, give us a 'Coo'.
- Are you going further inside?
- I'm not an idiot! I'll just run!
- Sire, there's nothing here.
- Huh?
Hey! He did shoot the arrow, right?
Yeah. He did.
King, isn't it better we
don't continue further?
- Shall we go?
- Yeah. Let's go.
Hey, go forward!
Dammit!
This is a good horse.
Listens to every single order.
He got coronated,
but we'll get cremated!
Hey! A stag!
[ARROW RELEASES AND STRIKES]
It's running!
Stop the chariot!
Bravo! What a shot, King!
A great shot!
I know.
Hey! Get it!
Annu, let's be done
with this and hurry home!
Kulashekhara, we'll carry
it in our chariot, okay?
People shouldn't think the
King returned empty handed.
The Brahma-rakshasa!
[OMINOUS ATMOSPHERE]
Great Lord, isn't it better
we leave now.. What?!
[HORSE GALLOPS]
He took my bow.
SOLDIERS!
[SOLDIERS GASP IN FEAR]
Fear not! Keep watch
in all four directions!
[ARROW STRIKES; ANNU COLLAPSES]
RUN!
[BODY THUDS AGAINST THE TREE]
Who was that?
Nagendra, stop acting like an idiot!
He was the last of the brave ones.
He's gone too.
If we all die, who’ll
tell our families?!
My God!
[SOLDIER SCREAMS IN HORROR]
[ARROW PIERCES]
Brahma-rakshasa's boulder!
Thus, we're done.
Stop staring and check it out!
Didn't you hear me? Go!
Good Lord!
[SOLDIERS CLASH WITH THE TRIBALS]
[TRIBAL SCREAMS FURIOUSLY]
GOD!
I made it out alive!
All thanks to the
guy in the sky!
[HEROIC MUSIC]
Wohoo! Berme!
Looks like I got here
a little late, didn't I?
[ROPE SNAPS]
♪ ♪
♪ The Ullaaya of the forest ♪
♪ The garden where Lord
Eshwara planted the flowers ♪
♪ The land shaped by Berme ♪
♪ The soil that holds the Daivas ♪
♪ This is the land of Kantara ♪
[TRIBALS CONTINUE TO SING]
Oh. Jabbanna's here.
You guys continue.
What are you children up to?
- Pampi...
- Oh?
How was my hunt?
Killed it, didn’t I?
You killed our damn spirit.
The next time you trail us,
we'll shower you with stones.
What nonsense are you blabbering?
You got scared and
ran like hell, right?
It wasn’t even a
tiger, just a porcupine.
It froze because I screamed!
Oy Grandpa! It spiked up and froze.
Hasn’t moved since. Take it.
Quit questioning my capability.
Give it to me! Argh!
Yeah, right!
Stop your nonsense.
You had no reason to test
your capability on me at this age.
[WOMEN LAUGH IN UNISON]
Nochchi! Take this!
There you go.
You led a good hunt today.
[MEN HOLLERING]
Ay Kura! What are
you always scratching?!
Abba, we had a great hunt today.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Huh?
[WARNING CALLS]
Hey! This one's alive!
[HUNTERS HOWL]
I died a long time ago.
- HEY!
- JABBANNA STOP!
He blacked out after seeing us.
Which scumbag brought him here?
They came by themselves.
- How many?
- Many.
We killed everyone
we laid our hands on.
The ones on the horses escaped.
It's the King.
The people of Bangra
have crossed the border.
They’ll try to drag our
people back into slavery.
Sleep with a weapon
under your head.
What cowards, man!
They ran without
even looking at us.
And they're scared of them.
My thought is, the people of
Bangra have already made the way.
Before they return, we
better cross it ourselves.
Should we tell
Jabba just to be safe?
Yeah, right!
He left our people behind
because they chopped his toes.
How will he even keep us safe?
I’m saying this because I’ve seen it.
Nah! You ran first!
I know what they’re capable of.
From now on, the border
watchers must stay alert.
- Berme!
- Yeah?
Dispose the bodies outside the border.
Let no more people
come looking for them.
Yeah. Sure.
Phew! Jabba said the same thing.
Cross the border!
What about the Brahma-Rakshasa?
- It's all a cooked up story!
- Really?
Berme, shouldn't we at least
know which direction to take?
We've got a guiding
spirit, don't we?
Dodda, hand me the axe.
If he’s been out this
long, I doubt he’ll wake up.
- Better to kill him, right?
- Yes!
- HEY!
- WAIT!
I'm back. Tell me.
Did we have to do this at
the edge of the waterfalls?
My legs are trembling!
What stone is this?
It's sharp as hell!
This isn't stone.
It's iron.
Our Sankappa makes them.
Don't eat iron.
Your tongue will rust.
- Hello! Sire?
- Yeah?
How far is your place from here?
It's a day's journey by walk.
- You'll take us, right?
- Sure. Wait!
Why do you guys want to come?
Shouldn’t we see
how far you’ve come?
And?
We'll return after, won't we?
If they find out that
I got you guys there
My life there too will
turn into a living hell.
Why do you think
you're taking us?
We're coming there drop you.
Sure that's what you think.
But they should get it, right?
God!
Okay then. Let's
pray to him and leave.
- What?!
- Yeah.
We're crossing the forest
boundary for the first time.
The rest is on you.
Bless us, Swami Panjurli.
Swami Panjurli.
[IN UNISON]
- What's happening?
- That is the Daiva we believe in.
I swear I don’t see anything.
You need true
devotion to see it.
Doesn’t matter. Just
pray with your heart.
I can now see it too.
I forgot to tell you.
Nobody but soldiers are
allowed to cross the border!
Now they will, won't they?
Good plan.
Phew! Thank God I'm alive!
I don't even wear anything inside.
Listen, what is a Brahma-rakshasa?
It's nothing.
- Once...
- Quiet. Let me tell him.
Once upon a time,
there was an evil king.
Wait, we have one too.
YEAH. HIM.
[IN UNISON]
He couldn't find anyone to work.
So he performed a great penance.
Why a penance?
He could have just paid more!
- Just listen. Will you?
- Don't interrupt.
Sages and saints offered
him a man as a helper and said -
"Give him so much work
that he has no free time."
Why's that?
If you let him free,
he'll eat humans.
- My God!
- Yeah!
- There's more.
- Let me continue.
You can stop here.
I’ve lost my zeal.
Already? Let me fill you up.
- There's more for you to know.
- This is enough.
- My heartbeat's really high.
- We'll stop that. Don't worry.
He did exactly as told.
When jobless, he
would gobble humans.
One time, he was about to eat the King.
The queen immediately
pulled out a curly hair strand,
and asked him to straighten it.
- Did he straighten it?
- No way!
He's still busy straightening
it out in the forest.
Who is this idiot?!
The Brahma-rakshasa!
- What?! Him?!
- Yep!
Good Lord!
What if he straightens it
and appears in front of me?
He'll straighten me out!
All I want now is to meet Jayanthi.
- Who's that?
- A chunk of the crescent moon.
Ah.
What's that?
Bangra's walls.
Did Sankappa build this too?
Yes. This was the first
move of King Rajashekhara.
Open the gates!
Berme, our clothes would've busted us here.
Shut up and walk straight!
Oy Chenna! The king
returned yesterday.
What took you so long?
Well, the forest had
plenty to explore.
- Then where's the prey?
- Right here!
Please shut your traps!
- Attending the King's first assembly?
- Maybe if I'm free.
What's taking the King so long?
The king rises early, meditates, prays,
then lights the lamp before coming here.
So, naturally he's late.
This is what I love
about you, King.
Even after taking the throne
You haven’t changed a bit.
You're still the same old Kulashekhara.
Bhogendra, It's noon already!
The assembly's waiting! Hurry up!
- We will.
- Noon already, huh?
Kulashekhara!
This is your first
assembly as a king!
They shouldn't find out we're drunk.
Nuh-uh!
No way they'll know!
[METALLIC OBJECT ROLLS DOWN]
Slow down! God!
Don't let them know
that you're drunk.
Hope they don't
know we're drunk.
No way!
Let the assembly begin.
Whoa man! What a spectacle!
Awesome, right?
- Hey!
- What?
Princess Kanakavathi is here.
She shouldn't spot us.
Yeah? Let's see if we can spot her.
- Let's check them out!
- Stop! I've somehow survived.
Don’t drain what little of me is left.
Guys! Listen up!
I mean it! Listen to me!
Gosh! Look at the crowd!
- Listen!
- What's that tall thing?
It's tall but doesn't
rise when needed.
Sir, please.
Where is he busy looking?!
[TASKMASTER ORDERS]
HEY! LIFT IT!
If your hands touch the
water, I’ll slaughter you.
[SLAVES SCREAM IN PAIN]
Genda!
What is it? Huh?
- Food!
- I'm dying out of hunger!
Wait right here! Don’t move!
God, I don’t know
who to control anymore.
- God! I can breathe easy now.
- One for me.
Looks like I should've gotten
them to eat before coming.
- Why are you acting like savages?
- Oh. Hey Chenna!
What?! Erm...
- Veera Mahabalanna.
- Long time. No see.
The king's assigned
me to secret service.
So, I can't be seen.
- Really?
- Super secret.
Eat. Don’t let your hands go dry.
Hurry and eat already!
Priest?
Please prepare a report
of everything done so far.
Let me know what else you need.
I will speak to the King
and arrange the permit.
I see a sacred stone.
Should we still sculpt it?
The Kadambas have commissioned
such a magnificent temple.
Shouldn't the God inside
look as good as the rest?
- You may begin.
- Okay. As you wish.
God! Protect us!
Looks like we’re off
to an inauspicious start.
[SCREAMS IN FEAR]
Hiding here? Stay in!
This is definitely a queen bee.
Hey! Come here!
- What is it?
- Are you a solider?
So only a soldier
can rescue you now?
Not leaving until they feed
you at my funeral, huh?
Hey! Who cares who she is?!
- Princess!
- I'm fine.
[TRIBALS ULULATE]
WOW! WHAT IS ALL THIS?
Cheenkara! Wipe your mouth!
You're drooling!
From here, we both go our own ways.
Don't tell anybody
that I brought you here.
Nah! We won't. Unless they ask.
What?!
Looks like I’m tomorrow's
fresh catch at the butcher’s.
Tch tch!
Hey! Chenna!
All that adventure
will finally pay off!
Hey!
Look here! We've found Sankappa's place.
Look at his inventions! What a genius!
- What did you want?
- Well...
Give me some of that.
Some of this. For hunting.
- A couple of these.
- What for?
To bring back our prey.
- The King's authorisation letter?
- You’ll give this only with that?
Did you join the army yesterday?
- Nah! This morning.
- Huh?
Hey!
Your armour's all dirty?
About that...
Gotcha! You came here right
after the training, didn't you?
YES!
If Sankappa was here, he
would've handed it over right away.
I managed to catch
you red-handed.
- Where is Sankappa?
- In the prison.
Whose son?
Jayanthi!
Where were you all these days?
Ugh. Never mind about that.
Your wife has found
out all about us.
- Which mongrel outed us?
- Veera Mahabalanna.
Ugh! All these wars
and he never dies.
To hell with him!
Enough hide and seek.
Come. Let’s speak, heart to heart.
Look over there and hammer!
I need to have a heartfelt
conversation here.
Okay.
- Aren't these things ours?
- Yeah man!
Fragrant! The cinnamon is great!
How did these things get here?
How much for this?
- Let's go!
- Take that off!
Even if you slog all your life you
won't be able to buy a handful of these.
- You think you can steal?!
- It's from our forest!
Men like you should be hung to death!
Soldiers! Let that be!
Grab him!
You keep him. This is ours!
We'll keep this.
Ay! Who the hell are you guys?
You don't look like soldiers.
Even with all this, if we don’t
look like soldiers, what’s the point?
- Don't take it off!
- All of them are thieves!
Soldiers! Come here!
Grab them! Hurry up!
- Frisk their clothes!
- Quit talking! Move!
- Guys! Listen!
- Keep moving!
- Don't you recognise us?!
- MOVE!
[TRIBALS ULULATE]
- Not all over again!
- Who is it?
Those demons! Move!
Where do I hide?!
Only God can guide me now!
Want me to go there?
These guys are all
over the king street!
Nab them! Go!
[BERME ULULATES]
Not the ride I wanted. Morons!
It won't be
comfortable up there.
We had enough down there.
Who asked you?
Get back to business!
My fate!
- Berme, looks like it's time to leave.
- Shut it!
[SPEARS CLANG]
Tighten your grip!
[CHARIOT WHEEL CREAKS]
♪ ♪
WOHOO!
[IN UNISON]
Is the procession on?
Who's pushing it?
It's us, Sir!
[CHENNA SCREAMS]
How the hell did
you get up here?
You got me here, right?
[FRANTIC SHOUTING AND SCREAMING]
[OVERLAPPING COMMOTION]
Scoundrels!
Don't you see?!
It's me! Chenna!
Scumbags! Let me come to you!
[BERME SCREAMS]
Who was that woman?!
Hey! He's here! Assemble!
HEY!
Behind my back, eh?!
Come at me!
Dodda!
Wait! No! Where are you going?!
Whoa!
Hold it tight!
I'll find a way out!
Why are you
staring like chimps?!
Jump to the side!
What's that noise?!
Dharu!
There's a turn ahead! Good Lord!
Stop the chariot!
Oh no! There's a valley at the end!
Lord Eshwara! Please save me!
I vow to break coconuts during
the Brahma-Kalasha! Good Lord!
[MEN SCREAM IN UNISON]
Give us some time!
We'll come by ourselves.
I just shat my pants!
After all, you needed
soldiers to rescue you.
Bring them!
- Princess!
- Hey, Chenna!
What are you doing with them?
I put my life on the line to arrest them!
JAI BANGRA!
[DRUNK DHAARU]
What is this?
- Country liquor.
- Specially made by us.
WHOA!
This packs a solid punch!
Yeah.
Keep this inside.
We shall leave now.
We've given it.
We shall take your leave.
Chieftain!
King, these men were
stealing goods in the market.
When questioned, they went
wild and damaged our businesses.
What is it.. your name?
Berme.
Where did you come from?
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
Kantara.
[STEEL CLASHES AS WEAPONS ARE DRAWN]
I hope the Brahma-rakshasa isn't here.
[CHAIN CLASHES]
[WHIP CRACKS]
I can't do this anymore.
They're built like buffaloes.
Kantara?!
[WHIP CRACKS]
Brahma-rakshasa.
You trapped my grandfather while
he was out hunting and killed him!
Treacherous brutes!
They don't bruise easily!
Whip them harder!
Bhogendra, their dummy
forest has nothing in it!
It's all a sham!
If you're truly your father's son,
you'd have stood your ground.
You'd have seen
that sham turn real.
The kid ran and I could
see his bum was on fire.
[MEN LAUGH IN UNISON]
[DIBBA] Don't laugh guys!
They'll beat us harder!
What are you
staring at them for?!
Go on! Whip them!
[OVERLAPPING GRUNTS]
Proud of beating tied-up
men, you scumbag?
Unchain me and come at me.
WHAT?!
S-C-U-M-B-A-G.
Please don't laugh!
They'll whip us harder!
Kulashekhara!
Step back!
Now!
[BHOGENDRA] We were only watching.
Who brought you to Bangra?
Is your Bangra
floating up in the sky?
Four steps and
anybody can find it.
We came by ourselves.
God! Save me!
- Hey!
- Oh. Chenna.
Where's your uniform?
I'm sick.
I came to ask the
commander for leave.
- Did he grant it?
- Yes.
Permanent leave. See you.
What about the secret service?
There are other men doing it.
My wife's easier to deal with.
Why did you come here?
You came to check on us.
Can't we do the same?
[BROODING MUSIC BUILDS]
Did you go to Kantara?
We didn't go inside.
We looked around the borders.
[MEN OF KANTARA LAUGH IN UNISON]
You knew you wouldn’t return home.
Yet you stepped onto this land?
[BROODING MUSIC BUILDS]
Back in the day, we
let you return home.
Today we barge into your kingdom,
beat your men, and stand before you.
You really think we can't go back?
[BROODING MUSIC BUILDS]
Come here.
NOW!
Did you drop some salt or poured it?!
Hey.
Nothing to worry!
Just asking him
if there's enough salt.
They've strolled in like it’s
a trip, hands swinging free.
Those hands must be cut...
He doesn't like an ordinary guy.
The way he carries himself, he
seems like he's the leader of Kantara.
Exactly! Exactly why I'm telling you!
We'll not get this
opportunity again.
He’s in our hands.
Let’s finish him.
Yep.
If you were in good company,
you'd understand a king's duty.
Keep cuddling your duty.
What will it be now?
Let’s not make enemies
of Kantara’s people.
Sigh! It's all in your
hands, isn't it, my king?
Do I have your permission
to wash my hands?
Hey!
Argh!
Hot water?! You wretched fellow!
[SERVANT SCREAMS IN PAIN]
Well...
MY CHILD!
[IN TULU] Sleeping, my child?
Wake up!
It's been a couple of
days since the children left.
Please make sure they stay safe.
Swami!
We've got prisoners.
Sell them to the
Arabs for a good price.
I can't just sell anyone man!
Want me to sell you?
I'll dress you like a monkey and sell!
You're giving me toothpicks
and are insisting that I sell them!
It's really difficult, Bhogendra.
Hey! Don't you dare call
me by my name, Booba.
- I'm now a minister.
- I see.
When I was guarding the King, your father
didn’t even know where babies came from.
Today, you're calling me
out by my name - "Booba!"
Hey! Where the heck is Booba?!
[IN PORTUGUESE]
- Hey! Excuse me!
- What do you want?
There's no space
to dock my boat.
What the heck is
this port even for?
- What did he say?
- He's a Portuguese trader.
He claims there's
no space to dock.
He's asking if the port
is only for decoration?
[SHARP SLAP]
You see there’s no
place to dock, right?
Next time, try
swimming to the port.
Get lost!
Son of a tramp!
Hey! What the hell did he say?
- He cursed your mother...
- Whoa! Calm down!
He just called you
an 'aggressive man'!
HEY!
Remember!
'The son of a tramp!'
Idiot! I'll take you to task someday!
- Honourable Minster!
- Yeah?
You shouldn't be laying
your hands on foreigners.
It'll ruin our trade.
Some folks only feel the
love when it comes with a slap.
The men I've got now are strong.
Shut your bum and sell them!
- Oy!
- Is food here?
Check out the strong
men you got last time!
Nothing! Checking
if you were alive.
Go back to sleep.
I thought food was here.
The men I’ve brought
today are no ordinary men.
They razed King
Street to the ground.
Our King Street?
How dare they!
These dacoits deserve to
be handled by my son, Peppe!
[INTENSE ORCHESTRAL SCORE]
Hand me the whip!
Swami is here.
[METAL KEY CLANGS]
[HEAVY METAL DOOR OPENS]
No matter how loud it gets
in here, you don’t hear a thing.
- Got it?
- Yes.
Latch the gates shut.
Pardon me?
Latch the damn gates!
Sure.
This isn't for the faint-hearted
Wait outside.
Okay. Hey! Get out!
No one comes back
until we order you to.
[WHIP CRACKS]
How dare you rob
under my watch?!
Lowlifes!
Where are you from?
Where did you come from?!
Kantara.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
What?!
Kantara.
Hurry up, dumbo!
I asked them to latch it and
morons have locked the damn gates!
What are you saying?!
Oy! If anyone's around,
please open the gates.
- Anybody out there?
- Is Swami calling us?
Swami told us to turn
deaf ears to all their cries.
It's me, Peppe calling!
Don't be afraid.
We are harmless!
HEY!
Morons! Hurry up
and open the gates!
My life's at stake!
I beg you! I'm suffocating in here!
Oy! Come here!
Ay! Sit down!
Thank god they're here!
- Remember you're bloody guards!
- What happened to Sir?
Keeps poking his head in
matters that don't concern him.
You call this guarding?
Where the heck did you go?!
We went to take a dump in the open.
– Together, like a squad?
Sir has ordered us to stick together!
Stick with me dammit!
Not on your own!
Where did you find
these numb-nuts?!
You'll have it from me!
Move, scumbag! Give me my sword!
Where are you off to?!
Mongrels! Get my head out!
- Close it!
- Now lock the gates!
All the shouting was of no use!
Don't come closer!
I'm a builder sure,
but I'm not into wood!
We won’t hurt you.
We’re humans, just like you.
Why did they imprison you?
My family has done
a lot for Bangra.
King Vijayendra asked
us to build a palace.
I built it.
His son asked us to build a prison.
We built that too...
Not even in my worst
dreams did I imagine
they’d use my own
prison to jail me.
S.. S.. Sankappa.
Whose Appa?
Yep.
I am that wretched man.
Sankappa! God!
Never did I imagine that I
would get to touch your feet.
Bangra's people said
these very words at first.
Do tell us. Why did they jail you?
The King asked for a ship.
- Did you build one?
- I did.
To test it, they made my trusted aide, the
Commander take the ship out to the river.
Right before our eyes, the ship sank,
taking the Commander down with it.
But why?
We’d made a tiny hole in the
bottom, just to drain rainwater.
But I never imagined water would
flood in through that same little hole.
Dammit!
That’s why you
don’t drink on the job.
Drink all you want after work.
That mishap actually
helped the Commander.
But that thankless fool
should remember it, no?
Hey!
What's that? A town by the river?
That's the market by the sea.
A port.
[DRAMATIC SCORE]
[PEPPE WALKS IN]
Looks like they're here.
[DOOR BREAKS OPEN]
[MEN GASP]
I haven't seen daylight in years!
Good Lord! Scoundrel's here!
You can come!
I'm holding the gate tightly!
Oy.
Quit staring and hold
the gate, scoundrels!
Don't worry. We're holding it from inside.
Heard you wanted to talk.
What's the matter?
Gosh!
We’ve got plenty more of that.
Let us out and we’ll fetch it for you.
We’ll give you half
And trade the rest.
He got hold of trading so soon?!
Not happening!
You've been sold for 1000
Varaahas to the Arabs.
What are you smoking?
Tobacco.
From beyond the seas.
It stinks.
I'll give you something.
Wanna smoke?
What is it?
You get some wild herbs in our forests.
Wild herb?!
Smoke it!
You'll be flying!
[TRIPPY MUSIC ENSUES]
[METAL CHAINS RATTLE]
What quality herbs, man!
Feels like the prison gates are wide open.
Sir, the cell gates are open.
Exactly.
- Sir Peppe!
- Enough. Give me some.
About us trading?
Tell me this.
You think saying "trade" a
few times makes you a trader?
Do you even know what it means?
Forget that.
Ever seen what
a port looks like?
Can we?
Nothing tops this.
I need to kiss the hands of
the saint who blessed us with it.
What are you doing?
Disgusting!
My old man never goes back on his word.
Saw the port, right?
It's dark. Now leave.
[BOOBA SNORING LOUDLY]
He dozed off?
[METAL LATCH CLANGS]
Done?
Yep.
You can't open it, can you?
No matter how hard I try, I can't.
Sleep.
We'll talk in the morning.
Sankappa, let's go.
We'll see you.
Don’t want them thinking
we left without a word.
Let Booba know once he's up!
What quality herbs, man!
You don't look like
someone from Kantara.
Oh no. I'm an Arab.
My father came to trade
and I was born here.
Looks like man
traded for a lot more!
Having seen the outside
world, Berme realized
his people needed
a leader to prosper.
Let’s start farming!
What does that mean, son?
Nothing tough. Let us grow
whatever we wish to eat.
♪ Prosperity.. Flourishing.. Produce ♪
♪ Prosperity.. Everywhere ♪
♪ Beneath the blue moonlight,
we witness our first harvest ♪
♪ Golden rays have ripened
into fruition in Kantara ♪
♪ Fresh gooseberries rest in our palms ♪
Go on.
♪ Learning to wield the
machines comes easily now ♪
Thank God! It turned.
♪ We’ve built stairs to the
floor above, a ladder to the sky ♪
♪ And now we dream in colours ♪
♪ Our eyes glimmer with a newfound light ♪
♪ Aaha! Ohoo! ♪
Phew! My job's done.
♪ Aaha! Yeheee! ♪
♪ Our gait has now got style ♪
♪ Aaha! Ohoo! ♪
♪ The forest shimmers with a gleam ♪
♪ Aaha! Yeheee! ♪
♪ Prosperity.. Flourishing.. Produce ♪
♪ Prosperity.. Everywhere ♪
♪ Beneath the blue moonlight,
we witness our first harvest ♪
Swami Panjurli has blessed us.
- Berme, it's a boy.
- Great.
It's great to see
your zeal in this age.
Come on!
By the time he grows up,
Kantara will have everything.
♪ ♪
♪ Ay! Plough and see ♪
- What is all this for, my son?
- For trading, Abba.
What does trading mean?
We barter this for what we need.
♪ Bask in this harvest song ♪
♪ Ay! Plough and see ♪
♪ Ay! Strive and earn ♪
♪ Savor the forest and hills,
bask in this harvest song ♪
♪ To give and receive,
the finest way to live ♪
♪ Trust your strength
and live your lives ♪
♪ Our eyes glimmer with a newfound light ♪
♪ Aaha! Ohoo! ♪
♪ This soil now yields fresh produce ♪
We no longer keep the third
share at the forest’s edge.
How long will you
live in fear of being
killed by them if you
step out of the forest?
When they live so arrogantly,
relying only on their puny soldiers.
Imagine if we, with the Daivas'
strength, set foot on their land.
♪ Prosperity.. Everywhere ♪
♪ Golden rays have ripened
into fruition in Kantara ♪
Old man! Don't drink too much!
You'll lose your bladder!
Ever since the
Kantara folks ran off
My life has been lost.
What will I do with this gallbladder, son?
We've got to do something to find them.
Done already.
If we nab them, I’ve made a vow.
To send my son on a
14-year exile in that forest.
That should work, right?
- Booba!
- Huh?
How dare you call
your father by name?
Scoundrel!
That wasn't me.
- Boobanna! [IN UNISON]
- Who?!
- Berme!
- Namaskara!
No! I'm not going to
the forest, Old man!
Jail these crooks!
- Now!
- What for, Boobanna?
We spent 1000 Varaahas of our own
to buy you, just to sell you to the Arabs.
That is our entire lifetime's
earnings, damn you!
Poor you.
Boobanna, we’ll trade right
here and repay your debt.
Really?
You've to repay.
- I swear on you.
- Okay. Go.
Good people.
- Old man!
- Yeah?
Did you just
permit them to trade?
Yes, Son.
Our loans need to be repaid, right?
- What about the Princess' permission?
- Huh?! What?!
NO!
Boobanna, you’re not the
kind to eat your own words.
We'll see you soon.
Dammit! Maybe I should
stop talking for a while.
All the women are so fair!
No need to prove your manliness here.
- Shush!
- Tell me this.
Wait, do you understand
the system of trading?
I don't.
But he does.
Hand it over!
What are they?
Looks like clothes.
Why do we need clothes?
Please trade without
a soul knowing.
How do we trade
without telling a soul?!
Well, stop shouting.
Everybody will know.
Man, he's really a moron!
Black pepper, cinnamon,
turmeric, cardamom.. cardamom!
Welcome!
Cinnamon, black pepper,
turmeric, cardamom.. cardamom!
[CROWD CLAMOURS]
There you go.
Look, we had no idea about
how valuable our products are.
Watching those once at
their feet rise to the occasion
didn’t sit well
with the people of Bangra.
Kantara's men are trading in our port.
I came by to inform the King.
I shall inform. Go on.
Bring Kantara's men to my office.
Princess?
Climbing is difficult for me.
Can I send my son instead?
Phew!
You've escaped the
prison and are now trading?
Unlike you, we're not trading humans.
Don't forget that you're in our land.
I don't think this is your land.
You’re just the supervisor.
Right Mr. Peppe?
It’s our calibre that
earned me this role.
If the Kadambas find out
there are others more able...
If they do?
Hey! Hey!
Don't go closer.
Why are you leaning?
We've given our own
produce from Kantara.
You've been trading till date.
From now, we'll
do our own trading.
I called you to give
you my permission.
Huh?! Permission for what?
Trading, obviously.
You've got to pay taxes.
How much?
A quarter of what you make.
Please pay that.
I don't have the
strength to borrow again.
- We'll see.
- I've filled him in, Princess.
The permit?
You've permitted trading.
But it shouldn't seem like we
sought your permission for it.
See you around, then?
These people are like that.
I’ll crush their arrogance.
He had to walk away
with a pomegranate.
[INAUDIBLE CHATTER]
Oy Dalal!
- He's down there.
- Okay.
Keep in mind, you're there to
trade, not do something stupid.
We'll try.
Son, careful.
Okay.
Oh! This is where
they get all their stuff!
Dalal!
Hey! Peppe!
Where's Booba?
Trouble with his
leg. He’s outside.
- Show me!
- Give it to him.
What have you got?
What do you want?
Bow and arrows.
[DALAL SNEEZES]
Don’t just grab.
Using it right matters.
You’ve never seen aim like ours.
Really?
- Cheenkara, how about we show them?
- Sure!
Hey!
Please listen to me, Berme!
They'll kill us if we go there!
Hey!
Oh! It landed there, eh?
You clueless apes!
[SPEAKS ARABIC]
Do you know the
value of these barrels?!
Bloody hell!
What is that?
12-year-aged spirit.
Toss that nonsense!
Who drinks such dated booze?
Let's go.
Hey! That's the speciality man!
You're not allowed
in this area, man!
Those horses are
meant for the king.
We're not doing
anything, Boobanna.
We're just here to see.
Wow! Such beautiful horses!
What if we pay more than the King?
HEY! BERME!
Not brandishing the sword.
I'm begging you.
Please don't touch it.
Fine man!
Not with our hands.
We'll use this.
- Oh no, Cheenkara!
- Genda, you scoundrel!
Careful, Old man!
If you touch it's ding-dong, you
expect it to kiss instead of kicking?
Catch it! Don't let it go!
[TENSE MUSIC]
- I'll tame this damn horse!
- Sir, the horse!
- Swami, run!
- How did it come here?
[STALL CRASHES]
Looks like this horse is in heat!
Rabid stud!
Huh?
Nice. Looks like my leg's working.
Princess, it's a stud. Be careful.
[COMMOTION ENSUES]
Who dared to touch the horse?!
Thanks to you, we'll have to behead it!
Go ahead.
Ever since I've stepped here,
I’ve been shaking things up.
Ask your king to be careful. Go!
If they won’t accept everything we
touch, they’ll have to give up a lot.
♪ ♪
Fast learner in
the trade, I see.
Still a lot left to learn.
I'm with you, right?
♪ O beautiful enchantress ♪
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ I’m now witnessing a
mesmerizing illusion before me ♪
Damn! Looks like we'll lose the port.
♪ You’ve swayed me with
emotions, O brave Shakuntale ♪
♪ Slowly, love poems have
blossomed in my heart ♪
♪ Arey! Something within me has changed ♪
♪ As if a rainbow has
become a part of me ♪
♪ This battle now feels
like a tender release ♪
♪ Have the bees flown
to the flower in longing? ♪
♪ Amidst history, has a chapter
of adorable poems opened? ♪
♪ O beautiful enchantress ♪
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ I’m now witnessing a
mesmerizing illusion before me ♪
Berme.
♪ A melodious panting, a
soothing sound of beauty ♪
♪ To cross the line is to commit a crime ♪
♪ With the spark in the
heart, let a radiant light begin ♪
♪ Like an intoxication
that keeps returning ♪
♪ Our eyes have kissed each other ♪
♪ Without wielding the sword, our hands
have etched the story of this new bond ♪
♪ Arey! Something within me has changed ♪
♪ As if a rainbow has
become a part of me ♪
♪ This battle now feels
like a tender release ♪
♪ Have the bees flown
to the flower in longing? ♪
♪ In the whirlpool of a river of pleasure ♪
♪ Our maiden’s heart has sunk within it ♪
♪ You’ve drawn me inside
the walls of love, O' sorcerer ♪
If your people find out,
you'll end up living with us.
That is why I came closer.
I wish to see the
Eshwara's garden of bloom.
Don't run behind a
firefly in search of light.
You'll lose your way.
♪ ♪
- Abba?
- Yeah?
Look at the value our
products have out there.
What is all this?
Next time we go, we
need to carry a lot more.
Come on!
You've scooped up
everything we had.
Where do we get more?
- Deep in the forest.
- Huh?
I've got some mixture
to make you look fairer.
Berme, don't be hasty and
enter the deep areas, okay?
Dibba, there's no going back from here.
You guys! Take all of
this and get back home!
- We'll explore further.
- Thank God! God heard us!
Sankappa? Where to?
Come with us.
I'm a respected man in Bangra.
Shouldn’t look like Sankappa went
for herbs and got eaten by the forest.
Not even a blade of
grass shall harm you.
We’ll guard you from behind. Come.
You’ve got no reputation
to save. Let’s go!
- Don't these tribals eat at all?
- Go on. Ask them.
Cheenkara, what's for dinner?
If it crosses us, it’s dinner.
Let's not dare cross him.
[ALARMED BIRDS CHIRP]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Sounds like a cuckoo, eh?
[BERME WHISTLES]
[DRAMATIC TENSION SCORE]
[TIGER GROWLS]
Oh! A tiger!
Run! It's here to make dinner
of anything that crosses it!
Looks like the tiger prefers Arab meat.
Dibba, it'll swallow
you whole. Back off!
[TIGER SNARLS]
AY!
[TRIBALS ULULATE]
[TIGER GROWLS]
[TENSE MUSIC BUILDS]
Must be a sacred stone.
Berme, when it
has left us alone.
Should we continue following it?
Where is the tiger taking us?
For a buffet! Just shut up!
Everybody! Let's go.
Let's see where it is taking us!
Sankappa, careful!
It's slippery here.
The moment I entered
Kantara, I slipped into history.
Something is going on in this forest.
- Stop scaring us man!
- You guys wait.
I'll go ahead and look.
That's better.
Our ancestors always told us that
there was a terrifying forest far away.
[OMINOUS ECHOES]
Berme!
[PIERCING SOUND]
How did the fire went off?
How did you come out of here?
- Why did you go alone?
- Okay. You two, follow me.
Glad he didn't spot me.
Let's find out what's
happening here.
[OMINOUS ECHOES]
[PIERCING SOUND]
Don't stay! Run!
I knew you guys
would turn up here.
Told ya, didn't I?
[OMINOUS ANIMALS SCREECHING]
Let's go.
Looks like I'll be the
victim of your bravado.
- Same here.
- You'll be fine. Walk.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Forget carrying the
produce from the forest.
Who will even carry
our bodies back home?
Good thing we came here!
Wohoo! Berme!
Found it, didn't we?
I only see you when
the lightning strikes.
Don't blame me if the
wrong chillies get chopped.
I'm warning you. Take this.
Gotta do something about dinner.
Will a jackfruit do?
Sure. Why not?
Don't act like a monkey!
Watch when you climb!
[MEN LAUGH IN UNISON]
What a chimp!
[DEBA ULULATES]
Deba!?
[MUSIC BUILDS TENSION]
[KNIFE CLATTERS IN SHEATH]
[BERME WHISTLES]
[MEN SHOUT AND CHARGE]
[BERME ULULATES]
[MEN ULULATE]
[BERME SCREAMS]
[EXHILARATING MUSIC]
[EPIC TRIBAL MUSIC]
[PIERCING SOUND]
[MEN SQUEAL IN PAIN]
[THUMPING FOOTSTEPS; SCREECHES]
[LORISES SQUEAK]
BERME!
[TIGER SNARLS]
[MENACING GROWL]
[TIGER ROARS]
[EXHILARATING MUSIC]
[INTENSE FOLK MUSIC]
Our son...
is dead.
Hey!
Get lost!
Get the heck out of here!
Irresponsible brutes!
You stepped out
and caused a ruckus.
Now, you've entered that
place and ruined everything.
- Jabba, let me tell you.
- HEY!
You worthless old man!
Why are you riling up the boys?
You can’t even lift a stick,
but want to get them killed?
We didn't go on our own.
We were taken.
HEY!
Who the hell took you?!
Huli (Tiger).
Did we just find a sacred stone?
O' Ullaaya!
While we live by placing
our faith in the Daivas.
They try to control those very
Daivas to seize their power.
The people of Kadapa.
They lied that their village was washed
away in the floods and came to us.
Can we get some space to join
the Eshwara's garden of bloom?
Give it to them.
We should've known the moment they uttered
the words, "Eshwara's Garden of bloom".
Someone must’ve told them
the story of sacred stone.
But the truth was...
They hadn’t come for
the garden’s flowers.
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
The moment they learned about the presence
of powers beyond their imagination...
Those wicked people set out to seize
the source of our Daivas.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[LORIS SCREAMS]
To seize the Daivas,
they made a collyrium from
the tears of Loris, a
primate, and smeared it.
[LANGUR FALLS WITH A THUD]
Their rituals started having an effect
on the nature around us and it showed.
[JABBA SCREAMS IN ANGUISH]
[COMMOTION ENSUES]
At that moment, to face them,
Goddess Parvathi sent someone.
The Huli (Tiger) Daiva.
Once it steps into Kantara, it will
only listen to its Ullaaya and do as told.
That day, they fled the forest.
Even now, they are trying
to seek power in a forest.
Today the same Huli Daiva
took you to their forest and
made you break the mystical
binding with your own hands.
[METAL CLANGS AND THUD]
[TRADITIONAL STRING MUSIC]
Mr. Raamadasa?
Kindly pause for a moment.
[MUSIC STOPS]
Kulashekhara!
I believe if your vocal cords
embrace this symphony...
It'll be fabulous!
- Friend.
- Yes?
- Just for you.
- Begin.
Mr. Raamadasa?
- Give me the rhythm.
- Sure.
Hurry up.
[TRADITIONAL STRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SINGS CACOPHONOUSLY]
My King?!
What's wrong?
You screamed?
Nothing.
King, the port officers are
waiting for an audience.
King, people of Kantara
have started trading in our port.
Let me check what this is about.
- Raamadasa?
- Yeah.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
When I see him with the Princess
It looks like he's
climbing onto your throne.
- Really?
- Yeah.
[METAL STRIKES NECK]
Hey Bhogendra!
Go and check out what's happening.
Don't take too long.
Behead and them return in a jiffy.
Ay!
Let's go!
- Darling.
- Let's go!
Guys! Look over there!
What do you want, dear?
[IN ARABIC]
Huh?
What do you want?
You took away my
will to live, didn't ya?
- Return that. Enough.
- Who are you?
OH! CHENNA!
Quit screaming guys!
When I found out you were
here, I snuck my way here.
Please take me to Kantara with you
Live or die, I want it to be in Kantara.
- Wife?
- Nuh-uh.
That's an annoyance.
This is...
Any way I'm starting a
new life, let her be with us.
- Let her!
Hey! I meant for me!
Fine. How did you find
out that we were here?
Not just me.
The whole of Bangra, the
King, and everybody else knows.
[TRUMPET BLOWS]
- Gunananda?
- Yeah?
The moment the chariot
halts, the praises should follow.
Only if I feel like it.
Halt!
Nope. Don't feel like it.
- The King of the Kings!
- Hey!
- The pride of Bangra's clan.
- Bhogendra!
- The power of King Kulashekhara.
- Goddamn!
The great Minister
Bhogendra has arrived.
Seemed like an overkill, huh?
He doesn't listen to me at all.
Scoundrel!
You'll get it from me!
Where is the royal traitor, Booba?
- Minister?
- Bhogendra, this side.
Treacherous rat!
You think you're ruling
Bangra's port, aren't you?!
[WHIP CRACKS]
People are watching.
Let's discuss inside.
Nope! This has to happen out here!
[WHIP CRACKS]
Please try and respect
my age, Bhogendra?
Respect?!
Take it!
[HEROIC SCORE]
Bhogendra, maybe it's
time you drop the whip.
- And if he doesn't?
- Hey!
- Raamadasa?
- Yeah?
[TRADITIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHIP CRACKS]
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Somebody call
the naval officers!
They're drowning, Minister!
You think a boat smith doesn't
know how to drown his ships?!
Old man, from now, I'm
with the men of Kantara.
We have to, son.
I've already vowed to.
Yep.
You think you can beat us, crush
the navy, and rule Bangra's port?
I doubt he thought of that.
- Glad you taught them.
- Bhogendra?
From now, this port belongs to us.
You don’t need anyone’s permission
or have to pay taxes to trade here.
Bangra doesn’t consume
what we touch, right?
I’ll make sure all
the world does.
[TRUMPETING CONCHES]
Scatter before the horn stops blaring.
Or you’ll be the last
victims of the human trade.
[TRADITIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
The chariot toppled.
Yep.
No!
You son of a tramp!
Looks like he's the
Portu-complainese.
What are you staring at, Kulashekhara?
Behead that moron!
Now that you told me to...
I won't.
This wretched man
has humiliated Bangra.
How can you spare him?
You spared the men of
Kantara, this guy's on our side.
I counted him as one of ours
and sent this worthless man.
That’s how the
port was lost today.
For having crowned you here...
You crowned me, right?!
For what freaking joy!
I’m just a namesake king
with no control over his army!
That woman who sniffed the Kantara
man’s sweat now runs the damn treasury.
- Grew up on those mongrels’ milk...
- Kulashekhara!
You're crossing your limits and...
I’m done staying
inside your limits!
From today, the army
and treasury answer to me!
I won’t seek your opinion
on any decision anymore!
It'll solely be mine!
Remember that!
I’m not prepared to hand you
the reins to end up on the streets.
I’ll take care of whatever
needs to be done.
Sit tight and watch me! Enough!
You called me to talk.
What is it?
You crossed the line by insulting your
own father in full view of the assembly.
He forgot I’m the King and insulted
me right there in the assembly.
Had you done your duty as a King,
you would've got all the respect you...
Enough!
Want me to spill the beans
about your love story?
What duty are you
even talking about?
Shut up and stay out of this!
They've defeated the navy
and have taken over the port.
Before the Kadambas find
out, we have to do something.
What do you plan to do, my King?
Let us call for a negotiation.
Will they agree?
We must give them what
they want and win them over.
I was wrong.
- Are those just words or...
- I truly meant it.
I know my actions
have humiliated you a lot.
Give me another
chance to fix everything.
Sit.
How do you plan to fix it?
I’ll do exactly what you’ve
never been able to do.
Won't even ask for your army.
You’ve already shown
what you’re capable of.
What worse do
you plan to do now?
Nothing big.
They dared touch our port.
I’ll trample their
'Eshwara's garden of bloom'.
Rajalakshmi.
Let's get Kanakavathi
married at the earliest.
I have no trust in him any more.
You placed the crown on my head.
Only I decide when it comes off.
These hands that crowned you
Know how to rip
that crown off too.
Watch how far your hands go, Appa.
If there’s a sword in these
hands, you won’t stand a chance.
Ay! Come at me!
Come at me, Mongrel!
We'll see who will be the
last man standing! Come on!
What's wrong?
Careful.
Oh no.
My King!
What happened?!
Amma!
Don't worry! I haven't poisoned him.
Let him have a worry-free
sleep for a few days.
[INTENSE MUSIC BUILDS]
I’ll wash away the dishonour on our
clan with the blood of the Kantara people.
Soldiers! Put this one in the prison.
He keeps waking your Grandpa
up and messing with his mind.
While we’re striving
to do good for Bangra,
you seem hell-bent on
burning it to the ground.
Yep.
Your jungle man is
strong and waiting.
Shall we marry you off to him?
He’ll make a fine son-in-law.
Kulashekhara is a dud.
Planning to make him
sit on the throne of Bangra
And rule it all by yourself, eh?
Go on. Put him to bed.
Sankappa, should we
have brought Boobanna?
If he finds out it's my
boat, he'd rather die.
[HOOVES CLATTER SOFTLY]
Eshwara's garden of bloom.
[KULASHEKHARA LAUGHS]
My grandfather stepped right here.
It's beautiful.
After him, I must be the only
one to have set foot here, right?
Huh?
Yea.. Yeah.
This forest. The darkness. The silence.
They're sleeping so peacefully.
Killing people in their sleep
is against the king's code.
Soldiers!
[DRUMS THUNDER LOUDLY]
[JABBAJJA LETS OUT A WARNING CRY]
Burn them to the ground!
[ARROWS FIRE]
GUYS! LET'S GO!
Friends! Kantara is now ours!
Have fun!
[WARRIORS CLAMOUR]
Poor people!
They’ve lived in the dark all these years.
It had to be me
bringing them light.
My Lord! What
wrong have we done?
You can't be touching
me. Move aside.
Poor guy! He died.
Listen, you'll be
fine. Drink water!
Drink it!
[CHILDREN WAILING]
[KULASHEKHARA LAUGHS]
Wohoo! Now whose bum is on fire?!
Attack guys!
Wild hens!
Gyaanadeva?
- Gorgeous, right?
- Hey! Go!
[SOLDIER FALLS TO THE GROUND]
[WOMEN SCREAM IN PAIN]
- Ajja?! Ajja!
- NO!
Ajja!
Damn! Where did my horse go?
My my! Irrigation!
[GENDA GRUNTS]
Genda!
S-C-U-M-B-A-G.
Grind the medicines and get it soon!
You guys douse the burning huts!
Oh no! The child!
What happ.. Oh!
[SWORD PIERCES THROUGH]
♪ Down on Earth to meditate Lord
Eshwara descended from the skies ♪
♪ Goddess Parvathi built
the garden of bloom for him ♪
♪ Today, mortals have set
fire to that garden of bloom ♪
♪ O Daivas, where art thou?
Our voices now cry for you ♪
♪ Perhaps Eshwara and Parvathi
would have come to our rescue ♪
♪ But why are you Daivas
not coming to our aid? ♪
[RHYTHMIC CHANT]
♪ ♪
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[IN TULU] Kantara is as special
as your god’s sacred place, Kailasa.
Today, the eyes of
sinners have fallen upon it.
Every living being here
has been condemned.
[DISTANT VOICE] Once we carried life
and death, yet now we can’t save this land.
Maanichilla!
(SUPPLICATION)
It's usually never done without us, right?
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
You reside in the stone.
Won’t you look upon the
sinners who’ve entered this land?
Won’t you free us from this
suffering your poor family is enduring?
♪ Righteousness stands
with the righteous ♪
♪ Truth upholds truth ♪
♪ On the path we walk,
there's poison, O' Ullaaya ♪
♪ They have slit through Mother Earth ♪
♪ Torn open her heart and seized it ♪
♪ Struck her with a poisoned axe ♪
[MAANICHILA CONTINUES]
Whoa! So this is your Daiva
♪ O God! They've ripped open the womb ♪
♪ Smashed it to pieces ♪
Where? I don't see a thing!
♪ Strangled our breath ♪
Hey!
He's an artist!
Won’t you look upon the sinners
who’ve entered this land? [MAANICHILA]
♪ The Daiva who protects us ♪
♪ Where have you disappeared? ♪
Who are you reaching out to?
I'm here now.
♪ Has the land of truth
been filled with venom? ♪
♪ The torment of
unrighteousness is upon us ♪
♪ O' Satyole ♪
My my!
I feel contented.
Let me give you your boon.
Hey! Bring them.
But with respect.
O' Ullaaya!
O' my Daiva!
O' Ullaa...
O’ protector of the forests!
Unite all your powers.
Come down from the sky
and step onto this Earth.
Punish the sinners and wipe
their footprints off its face.
Lay your eyes on them
and shatter their hearts.
Let a single blow from you
flood the land with their blood.
Looks like the
Brahma-Rakshasa ran away, eh?
HEY!
Hey!
Where did you abandon
your people to die?
- Abbe!
- Berme!
Your Amma?
She's got a great voice.
AY!
ABBE!
Crush their arrogance and
come save the Dharma, O' Guliga
ABBE!
[BERME QUIVERS]
No! Abbe!
[GULIGA SCREAMS]
My child! Have you reached my lap?
Swami Guliga!
[GULIGA IN TRANCE]
Baidi?
Sound the drums!
[INTENSE DRUM BEATS]
[GULIGA IN TRANCE]
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
[INTENSE DRUM BEATS]
Whoa! A dance performance, eh?
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
Before committing these atrocities
on the land of Swami Varaahamoorthi
HEY!
Are we here to
watch his tomfoolery?!
Grab him!
Rudra Guliga.
Hey!
Didn't you realise the
sinners will be punished by
Kshetrapala Guliga, the
protector of this realm?
Raahu Guliga.
Tantra Guliga.
[BODIES THUD]
[EERIE NOISE]
Kattalekaana Guliga.
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
Huh?
Nettara Guliga.
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
Agni Guliga.
For every sin you have committed, I will
offer your blood to this soil like flowers
And uphold Dharma!
Swami Raja Guliga.
[KULASHEKHARA SCREAMS FOR HIS LIFE]
[BERME GASPS]
[BERME FALLS WITH A THUD]
♪ ♪
♪ When a man strikes his
toe on fate’s cold stone ♪
♪ The hurt refuses
to mend with time ♪
♪ The wicked shed
blood in Dharma’s name ♪
♪ Yet their laments
cannot silence the Daivas ♪
♪ The thunder that
roars to devour the earth ♪
♪ Breaks into hiccups longing
for Mother Earth’s embrace ♪
♪ ♪
♪ O' an injured womb
is a painful fate ♪
♪ Yet you wander all
your life to find a cure ♪
♪ Unaware of the conflict
with an unseen foe ♪
♪ You lose yourself in
the quest to find yourself ♪
♪ Despite washing away
our sins, Goddess Gange ♪
♪ Leaves you and me
suspended in repentance ♪
♪ The proud garland of
fresh flowers you wear today ♪
♪ Might wither away by tomorrow ♪
♪ ♪
Hey! The King's up!
Give him water!
♪ Life is a curse more
dreadful than death ♪
♪ The cure for sorrow
lies within the pyre ♪
♪ There is an end woven
into every beginning ♪
♪ Yet you walk through
life without a clue ♪
♪ The mother’s bosom milk
seems to have turned into blood ♪
♪ Tell me what share of sin
one owes in the sins committed ♪
♪ The door-sill that sought
to cross fate’s bounds ♪
♪ Seems to have become
the hook in fate’s play ♪
♪ ♪
Oh God! No!
King, Lord Eshwara's statue
sculpted for the sanctum has cracked.
[MUSIC SWELLS EMOTIONALLY]
- Who is he?
- Peppe. From Bangra's port.
So good people do exist.
When you’ve humiliated
Eshwara’s elements
Do you think he’ll
dwell in your temple?
It’s not a stone that
cracked, but his heart.
How do we fix this?
Until he's happy, the
Brahma-Kalasha cannot be instated.
What can I do?
There's peace in this place.
Tie it over there.
Keep bringing it.
How can you keep
refusing food, Jabbanna?
Have it.
Berme, I can't live like this.
Come on, Jabba.
How can you say this?
What do I do?
Are we prey for them
to hunt us at will?
We’ve been left too weak to face them.
We won't just face them.
We have it in us to fight them back!
Amma would say that a tree can
only stand tall if its roots run deep.
[WARNING DRUMS]
[SOLDIERS SCREAM IN PAIN]
We don't kill women and children.
Take another step
and we won't hesitate.
Please give me a
chance to explain myself.
Watch it.
Their people will behead
anything we touch.
I know we've caused
you a lot of pain.
Like you, we too have lost much.
You should've known, the fire
you lit in our place would burn you.
Before crossing borders in
greed and provoking our people,
you could have
thought of it too.
Who drew the borders?
The ones who ran away
or those who stayed in fear?
If you cross, it's power.
If we do, it's greed?
What power?
The respect we had among
vassal kings is now on the streets.
The crown meant for the
throne has rolled to the floor.
Go and repent for your sins.
That is why I'm here.
The very powers
we've disrespected...
We wish to mark a special space in Lord
Eshwara's sanctum, pray there and repent.
Who are you to make
space for our Daivas?
We live in the
land they gave us.
Don't let ego stop this.
This is a chance for all
of us to live as equals.
You enslaved our men and shed
their blood to build your kingdom.
You filled your treasury
with loot from our forests.
And now you speak of equality?
This is the only path
left to right our wrongs.
Please allow this.
Even if we agree, our
Daivas won't go with you.
Are these your words?
Or your Daivas'?
[TRADITIONAL FOLK MUSIC]
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
[IN TULU] He's the
son I gave birth to, right?
So this isn't easy for me.
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
Over there, my Ullaaya's
heart has been broken, kids.
Just like I protected you, isn't it my duty
to bow down and guard the Almighty's home?
There’s some astonishing
truth hidden in my ways.
Let that remain a secret
between me and my Ullaaya.
It's not them calling us.
It is my Ullaaya, the Almighty.
Let no worries trouble your mind.
Let’s just go once and
see for ourselves, what say?
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
[EMOTIONAL VOCALS]
♪ ♪
♪ Lord Shiva, we know
not the path of devotion ♪
♪ All we know is to pray with our hearts ♪
♪ Ullaaya, where your presence dwells ♪
♪ Where the mystic power abides, we come ♪
♪ Now, you must save us ♪
♪ All we know Lord Shiva,
is to pray with our hearts ♪
- Who is he?
- Emissaries of Kadamba.
♪ ♪
♪ Om ♪
♪ Among the Ganas, we
invoke you, O Ganapati ♪
♪ The most renowned
among all poets and scholars ♪
♪ The eldest among Devas,
Lord of the Brahmanas ♪
♪ O Lord, we bow to you,
the protector of the sacred ♪
♪ Purified by a sacred bath,
clad in garments of purity ♪
♪ We come to you with
folded hands in prayer ♪
It’s tradition for those from
the forest to build the chariot.
- And now...?
- We’ll take over that duty from now.
♪ For the welfare of the world ♪
♪ We consecrate this statue ♪
♪ Uniting Shiva with
his boundless Shakti ♪
♪ We chant, declaring
our devotion to you ♪
♪ May our mortal
abode be made pure ♪
♪ May our minds flow in peace ♪
♪ This dwelling of ours is the temple ♪
♪ All goodness in the world
is the Almighty’s blessing ♪
♪ The divine power shines resplendent ♪
♪ True happiness lies
in the wealth of virtue ♪
♪ Where lies diligence and devotion ♪
♪ There comes victory ♪
♪ The divine mind resounds ♪
♪ All we know Lord Shiva,
is to pray with our hearts ♪
♪ ♪
[VEDIC CHANTS FOLLOW]
[INTENSE DRUMBEATS]
In the land created by
Parashurama, you’ve played a noble
role in installing the Brahma-Kalasha
at Lord Shiva’s temple.
I pray to God that we are all blessed with
prosperity, good health, and abundance.
The Kadambas honour you
with a gold statue as a souvenir.
I request you all to
accept it with devotion.
Kindly sit.
- Can we touch this?
- Yes.
Despite all the
differences, you’ve fulfilled
everything Bangra
asked of you, beautifully.
This is a historic decision.
I congratulate you for this, on
behalf of all the people of Bangra.
Ask nicely, and we’ll
do anything for you.
I know.
You don't.
If you did, your son would
be sitting on that throne.
[INTENSE MUSIC BUILDS]
Okay.
I'll ask you something nicely.
Will you give it?
I know what you’ll ask for.
We only needed the port to trade.
Not to rule over it.
We’ll return it to you.
But I have one condition.
Ask.
Release everyone who was
forcefully turned into slaves.
Daivas have now been
established in this soil.
May you walk the path of Dharma.
Now this is a historic decision.
I congratulate you for this, on
behalf of all the people of Kantara.
Good work. Keep going.
Brave effort. Push through.
Why did you stop?
If it gets too hot, what if it melts?
Is that your father’s..
to just melt away?
Keep pumping!
Once upon a time, you
were a prisoner in my cell.
Time changes, Peppe.
- We need to change with it.
- I learned.
While pumping the air?
[PIG SNORTS]
With his pot of sins full, the King
now walks the path of Adharma.
Will you take a step to make sure
Bangra doesn’t burn to the ground?
Or will you follow the one wearing
anklets and step on a bed of burning coal?
The choice is yours.
You dare use our Daivas and
devotion to cover your dirty deeds?
You want the Daiva, eh?!
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
[PEOPLE OF KANTARA CELEBRATING]
They’ve been through hell their
whole lives and are finally breathing free.
Watching them happy
gives me a sense of peace.
Why are you sleeping instead
of witnessing this, Abba?
I am watching.
But there's still so much
more for you to see.
Come with me.
Berme!
When we stray from the path, we
need someone to guide us back, right?
So, I came to visit you.
Beware of those who yearn
for Eshwara’s garden of bloom.
Don’t ever trust them, my son.
Amma?
[MAN WEEPING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[MAAYAKAARA WEEPING]
[WOMAN CRYING]
[MEN AND WOMEN WAILING]
Oh no! Berme!
[PEOPLE CONTINUE TO WAIL]
Swami Sathyole, our innocent
children have fallen unconscious
and a pandemic has
struck us like a demon.
Whether we live or
perish, it's your call.
You, the mystical
power, come alive in form.
Rid us of this disease, take away
people’s pain, Swami Sathyole!
Somebody has trapped the Daivas.
[SORCERER GRUNTS]
The people of Kadapa.
Why is this known as
Eshwara's garden of bloom?
Beware of those who yearn
for Eshwara’s garden of bloom.
Eshwara's garden of bloom.
[BAIDI CHOKES]
Nourish her with the
milk of our women.
We shall raise the child for a while.
It'll be alright.
Our son...
is dead.
Don’t ever trust them, my son.
Anna (Brother)!
But you can't do it, can you?
Don't end up burning your hands.
Somebody has trapped the Daivas.
Even if we agree, our
Daivas won't go with you.
Are these your words?
Or your Daivas'?
Eshwara's garden of bloom.
I was once afraid of the forest’s
powers and refused to go to war.
Kanakavathi!
Kantara must become ours.
The stones of their Daivas should
become the steps of our palace.
That won’t be so easy.
He didn't come just
to install the deity’s idol.
He was here to anchor Dharma.
Don't be afraid.
There’s one last task to complete
to make your wish come true.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
I have no patience left
to wait, Kanakavathi.
My sword is thirsting for their blood.
We don’t have the
strength to fight him.
Who else does?
The child who once lay frozen,
unable to move, now sits on the throne.
She didn’t survive
death for nothing.
Bangra’s blood and Kadapa’s breast milk
Both carry poison.
It must not seem that
the King of Bangra put
his daughter at the
forefront of the war.
You wield the blade.
I'll give you the support.
I was happy thinking that by the time they
grow up, Kantara would have everything.
Today, we can't bear the
sight of these lifeless children.
All these years, those
Daivas protected us.
Their eyes must be
weeping blood now.
The spark they've lit
on our faith should grow
into a wildfire and
burn them to the ground.
- But, Berme...
- We can't stay silent any more, Jabba!
This isn't a war for our gain.
It's a battle for the Daiva
stones under their control.
They say, to destroy Adharma,
Lord Shiva keeps sending his Ganas.
Today, every soul in Eshwara’s
garden of bloom stands as a Gana.
[TRIBALS LET OUT A ROUSING CHANT]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[EAGLE SCREECHES, ECHOING]
Were they doing a re-con to
count how many of us are here?
[COLLECTIVE GASP]
[FOOTSTEPS RUMBLE]
[INTENSE MUSIC BUILDS]
[BROODING BEATS]
We’ve bound all of Kantara’s
Ganas through mystic sealing.
If a more powerful
force tries to enter
I'll handle it.
To fight Berme, who comes
from the source of all powers
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS]
The strength of three
generations must rise.
[BERME SCREAMS IN RAGE]
[WARNING GONG SOUNDS]
[ARROWS FIRE]
[BERME SCREAMS IN RAGE]
[WAR CRY]
[ARROWS THUD AGAINST SHIELDS]
[WHEEL GRINDS]
[EXPLOSION SOUND]
Hold your shields!
Dammit!
Hold them around me, mutts!
[BLOWS CONCH]
[BURNING LOG RUMBLES]
[DOOR BREAKS OPEN; MEN GASP IN FEAR]
Whoa Sankappa!
Bangra's wall has shattered!
Wouldn’t the one who built the
wall know how to tear it down?
Hail Kantara!
♪ Who dares to bind the fire? ♪
♪ For the chains themselves
were forged in flame ♪
♪ Who dared touch
Kantara and walk free? ♪
♪ Destruction fills the kingdom,
a deafening, pitch-black night ♪
[WAR CRY]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ It has been here
from the very start ♪
♪ The sky, the mountains, the
earth, the endless blue sea ♪
♪ It belongs to all ♪
♪ No father holds the
right to give it away ♪
[BERME SCREAMS IN RAGE]
♪ ♪
[BERME'S ARMY ERUPT IN RAGE]
Inform the King!
♪ ♪
♪ Are you watching? The strength we wield!
Come at us! ♪
Never in my dreams did I think
our foolish hunt would spark this war.
♪ ♪
♪ With the blessings of Eshwara
and Parvathi, with the words of valour ♪
♪ Hey King, who boasts
of building forts and walls ♪
♪ The forest warns - Beware! ♪
♪ The wild fire has risen,
blazing at the city's gates ♪
♪ Who dares to stop it when
its flames reach the sky? ♪
♪ Scream with all your might! Beware! ♪
♪ Beware! ♪
♪ ♪
GOOD LORD!
Go to the doctor. Hurry!
Do you need a...?
Where are you running to, you mongrel?!
Swami, we're with you!
♪ Hey King, who boasts
of building forts and walls ♪
♪ The forest warns - Beware! ♪
♪ The wild fire has risen,
blazing at the city's gates ♪
Dodda!
♪ Who dares to stop it when
its flames reach the sky? ♪
Go ahead.
Where do I look in this dust?
♪ Hey King, who boasts
of building forts and walls ♪
♪ The forest warns - Beware! ♪
♪ The wild fire has risen,
blazing at the city's gates ♪
♪ Who dares to stop it when
its flames reach the sky? ♪
♪ Scream with all your might! Beware! ♪
[VOCALISING]
They've crossed the border.
Hold them till sunset!
[BATTLEFIELD GRUNTING SOUNDS]
[GYAANADEVA SCREAMS]
♪ With the blessings of Eshwara
and Parvathi, with the words of valour ♪
♪ Hey King, who boasts
of building forts and walls ♪
Jayanthi!
- You...!
- Hey!
Are you here to win a
war or wag your tongue around?
Mongrel!
♪ Courage is the weapon against arrogance ♪
♪ Righteousness
is the cure for hatred ♪
♪ We kneel before no one ♪
♪ We stand, ready to fight! Hail us! ♪
♪ The sky belongs to the
eagle, limitless and free ♪
♪ Does the forest not shiver?
Hear the elephant’s mighty trumpet ♪
Hey!
Oh. Chenna!
Stop staring! Look behind.
Death's approaching!
[SOLDIER SCREAMS AND CHARGES]
[BLADE IMPALES]
Woman, this one’s death-proof. Let’s go.
♪ Hey King, who boasts
of building forts and walls ♪
♪ The forest warns - Beware! ♪
♪ The wild fire has risen,
blazing at the city's gates ♪
♪ Who dares to stop it when
its flames reach the sky? ♪
♪ Scream with all your might! Beware! ♪
[WAR CRY]
[WAR CRY IN UNISON]
[EERIE MUSIC]
[POSSESSED RAJASHEKHARA GRUNTS]
[POSSESSED RAJASHEKHARA SCREAMS]
King.
Ajja!
I want the Eshwara's
garden of bloom you desired.
[FLAMES CRACKLE]
[HORSES GALLOP; GROUND TREMBLES]
♪ With the blessings of Eshwara
and Parvathi, with the words of valour ♪
[HORSES WHINNY]
[WARRIORS CHARGE IN RAGE]
NOCHCHI!
[CHEENKARA CHOKES TO DEATH]
Ajja?
The guardian of Kantara.
[VOCALIZING]
I need to break the spell.
How do I do that?
When they found you in that well,
no one knew who or why they left you.
Today is the day you tell
the world why you came.
Go on!
Gange will show you the way.
The King of Bangra!
Go on!
Did Lord Eshwara come here?
He didn't just come here.
He lived here.
Is he still around?
He's in there.
Care to see?
[BERME THUDS ON THE GROUND]
Today is the day you tell
the world why you came.
Go on!
Gange will show you the way.
[BERME GASPS FOR BREATH]
[ROCKS CRUMBLE]
[POSSESSED RAJASHEKHARA CHOKES]
[MAAYAKAARA GASPS]
Protectors of Kantara, no
matter how many, try me.
I shall drench your
Daiva stones in blood.
Ullaaya!
[EXHILARATING MUSIC]
[DEEPLY RESONANT GROAN]
[GROANS CONTINUE]
[GROAN GROWS CLOSER]
[BRAHMA-RAKSHASA BELLOWS]
[BERME GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[BERME GROANS IN PAIN]
AY!
[ROUSING MUSIC BUILDS]
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
[APPROACHING RUMBLE]
♪ ♪
[TIGER GROWLS]
This is my prey!
♪ ♪
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
[TIGER ROARS]
Smearing soot on your body
and waving a rusted trident
doesn’t make you Eshwara’s Gana.
Standing before you is
the womb of all creation.
A woman.
If you've got the
guts, try touching me.
Come
[IN TULU] You're a disgrace to
women and I'm not the one to touch you
To destroy you once and for all
Mother Sankebaare, the
daughter of Gaalibhadra Kumara
My sister!
My sister's coming for you!
[GAGGARA JINGLING SOUND CLOSES IN]
Can you hear it?!
[SOUND GROWS LOUDER]
[DUAL VOICE RESONATES]
The origin of creation you mentioned, in
the form of Chavundi, I stand before you
I shall crush your skull!
And mend the broken
heart of Lord Shiva!
Chavundi.
[KANAKAVATHI SCREAMS IN RAGE]
Just a young hen, after all.
[NECK SNAPS]
[RAJASHEKHARA SCREAMS IN ANGUISH]
Light!
In light, everything is visible.
But this is not just light
It's a vision.
The light which will shine
on the past and the future.
Do you see it?
[PRIMORDIAL SCREAM]
♪ ♪
♪ Varaha, the Supreme among all Gods ♪
♪ He who assumes the form of a Wild boar ♪
♪ With teeth as hard as Diamond ♪
♪ He who protects us like a shield ♪
♪ ♪
♪ He who embodies the essence of Shiva ♪
♪ The one who thrives on Earth ♪
♪ He who gives refuge to
those who believe in him ♪
♪ The one who has won the
hearts of thousands of Gods ♪
♪ We now stand in front
of you, worshipping you ♪
♪ ♪
- Did he also disappear right here?
- Yeah.
What happened to
the cave down here?
That's a legend for another day.