I'm not angry.
I'm not asking for special treatment.
I'm just angry.
You said I was one of your best guys.
Was.
But if you can't hire me back, just ask
them to take me off the blacklist.
Say that again, and I'll kick you and
your kid out on your ass.
Bringing her here to guilt me.
Look, I need to work.
She said her fever for the last weekend.
That ain't on me.
I'm not the jerk that spoke to a union
rep about radiation exposure one time.
You got your daughter.
Your nuts didn't fry.
Take the win.
Bye -bye.
Sick kid in my office.
You know, I didn't bring her here to
kill you.
And this is you not angry?
Thank you.
Are you man enough to risk it all?
Today is your last chance of the year to
be on The Running Man.
If you can duck the boys in black, the
public, and McCone's hunters for 30
you'll run away with a billion new
dollars.
Go on.
I'll give you a head start.
That's easy, Tim, motherfuckers.
If you've got the cash, if you've got
the balls, don't miss the final run of
season.
Don't worry.
Daddy's not that crazy.
To feed the wheel, we're a big -boned
badass that bravely would bag a big box.
Am I right, bud?
And away we'll go.
But for 100 new dollars, the capital of
France is A.
Marseille, B. Lyon, or C. Paris.
Paris! C!
Collect!
Cynthia,
drop a hundo in the hammy.
Oh, look at the fuzzy hamster.
Did you see the fuzzy hamster? No.
Next question. For 1 ,000 new dollars,
how many laboratories does a net air
flying V luxury jetliner have?
Is it A4, B5, or C6?
It's A, B, bud.
It's A.
She said, since 12 o 'clock, the rich
are even more full of shit than they
thought. But
in
my hand is the question that contains
your life.
Who invented the Babylonian?
But we hardly knew yet.
Okay. How's she doing? Mommy.
How's she doing?
She's really burning up. Hey. Good
night, Mommy.
I need to guide you here.
Can I help?
She's hurting bad.
That's not good.
Two drops.
All right.
Wait, what is this?
Look, I know.
Molly said he would have real farms,
damn it. Real flumets. Yeah, well, a
black market buddy has all the stuff to
kill people, but it's sold out on the
things to save them.
All right.
This stuff doesn't make her better,
babe. But it makes her feel better.
Look, I just pulled another double at
the Hellhole Club, and if it wasn't dead
in the morning, I'd still be there. So,
that's what we can afford today.
I talked to him.
What, you did?
Who punched Kathy?
Took her with me.
I didn't, you know, kill Trip. No, I
mean, Trip wouldn't beat the crap out of
him.
Smart. I left my pride at the door. I
was respectful.
Maybe got a little heated at the end,
but by then it was game over.
They don't want us to win.
I'm sorry, Adley.
I tried.
Hey, you're just being punished for
being a good man.
You were just standing up for your guys.
It's just the same thing, right? You
know, I got to be a dad and they didn't.
Ben, none of this is your fault.
It doesn't change our situation.
No.
We're in it together, right?
Wait, where's your son?
Oh, Ben, those take forever to make. No,
no, it was on when we got home. Hold
on. It's here. It's here. Those are her
comfies, babe.
Shh.
When did you kick that off?
Shh. Don't worry.
Dadda's gonna find it.
Get it together, girl.
Honey, are you going back to the
Libertine? I don't want to. I thought
that place was dead in the morning. It
is.
Except for the most desperate wasted
loser.
My friend told me how to get tips out of
these guys.
The other waitresses do it all the time.
No. Look, if these jerks can flash 50
ND per rattle, they can accidentally
save a kid's life. Babe, I can't let you
that. Ben, she is burning up.
Look, my friend makes 20 new every
fifth. Usually it's just one customer.
Hey, now, you know I never do that.
My friend doesn't even let him grab her
ass.
She just charms them into tipping for
something that's not on sale. And right
now it's prime time for that kind of
play. No, it's the wrong exec.
Thinks that you ripped him off. You
could end up in the dump like that girl
across the street. I'm sorry. These men
are savages. If we don't get real farms
from a real doc, she won't survive
another night.
We don't have a choice.
Yeah, we do.
Where are you going?
Get money.
Enough for her to see a real doc before
bedtime.
You actually mean about taking chances?
People on that show never come back. I'm
not trying out for the running man.
There's a ton of other shows. Look, the
lowest amount someone won today, $75 new
dollars. I get on one of those, we get
the meds. Oh, no. People on these games
get hurt, Tim, like, really bad.
Kid stuff makes the kind of jobs that
work.
Hey.
Promise me you won't go on that show.
I promise.
Hope you enjoy it.
Even if you're never ready to get up
there.
Network building.
Tryouts.
Thank you.
He's going to try out.
Hey, this guy's in trouble. Shut up and
get back to the line. This guy needs
help. No helping. Step back. Get him a
fucking doctor and I will. I said step
back now.
Keep moving, people.
Nothing to see.
Back to the line.
Well.
to be faster ben richards 35 married
employment history hired by cgen fired
for insubordination why is there a red
triangle on my file hired by net utility
fired for hey man i asked you a question
insubordination
hired by the fence for the daughter
fired for
insubordination poor kid you mentioned
my daughter again they don't make glass
thick enough To stop me from joking you
out.
Elevator six.
Next.
Please stay.
Hey.
Go up 27, right?
Yeah. 29, neighbor.
Loughlin.
I'm Tim.
Tim. Jampy.
Jampy's my last name, and Tim is short
for Timothy.
Got it.
Should we all go around and say our
names in a fun fact?
We can do it later.
What's that?
I got you.
Thanks.
You didn't have to do that.
No problem.
You'll help him, Will.
Obedient. Never.
Heroism. Useless.
Technology.
Abuse. Freedom.
Nope.
Authority. Burn.
Anarchy. When?
Just it.
Hilarious.
Family.
Everything.
Next image. What do you see?
Cutest puppy ever.
What about this one?
Oh, it's my favorite flower.
Giving me a hug.
Final image. Tell me about it.
Infinite bunny.
Can you suck into a nice tornado, spring
blood all over the galaxy?
Mr. Richards, you are quantifiably the
angriest man to ever audition for our
show.
Well, that really pisses me off.
Proceed directly to your next
destination.
Final assessment.
Ooh, our jumpsuits are in here.
You're required.
To change into your size jumpsuit.
You're on the fuck out.
Bang, bang. Nice.
You must wear your designated jumpsuit.
Yo, you got a target on your back.
Yo, Richard.
Knew it would be us, man.
Knew it would be us.
Come on, shit happens, right?
Ooh,
that's us.
They say you run to add life to your
day.
Not days to your life.
That's it, both are pretty fucking true.
Don't miss the final run of the season.
I always thought this was fake, but... I
don't know.
Feeling pretty real now.
Right, guys?
Feeling really -osa.
second, y 'all.
Later.
Miss Laughlin?
Hey, uh, you're the man, Richards.
Never would have made it without you.
You like spaghetti?
Hey, so far, so good.
Don't worry, we'll keep it down.
Mr.
Richard?
Eat a non -aspericulum.
There's not death that man should fear.
You're never beginning to live.
Dan Killian.
Go ahead.
Relax.
No, critics say The Running Man
represents a return to the barbarism of
Roman Colosseum.
I disagree.
I'm not doing The Running Man.
I'm aware of your family crisis.
And I think the contents of this
envelope will help.
If we come to an agreement, it's yours
to keep.
Call it a signing bonus.
I'll do any other show.
The most anyone's ever won on another
show is a thousand ND, and I know it
sounds like a tremendous sum, but it's
not enough to get your family out of
slumside for good.
Whereas on The Running Man, merely
surviving a single week would put the
Richards in the top 1 % of global
wealth.
See for yourself.
Page 66.
I'm not trying to get myself killed.
Mr. Richards, I'll be honest with you.
I've said this to every contestant, but
this is the first time I've really meant
it.
You have what it takes to win this game.
Our viewers have a burning desire to see
a runner go the distance, and we've had
men come close, 29 days in season one.
But it's going to take somebody special
to go the full 30.
You tested off the charts, so I looked
through your employment history and had
my assistant shoot me your highlights.
Now this is the most thrilling 10
seconds of video I've seen all year.
Well, they fired me for destroying the
harness.
But you bounced back.
Hired by DefenseNet, the best wages
downtown.
No best dog shit, still dog shit.
Then why beg to be rehired?
Let's be honest.
You stuck your neck out one too many
times for your coworkers and got your
chopped off.
Pretty gutsy, considering half the
country thinks union should be illegal.
I come from the other half.
So you can dismiss twice.
Right there is why you can win this
game.
You're a fighter, Richards.
Network blacklisted you from all the
corps they own, except for this one.
You risked your life for other men and
their families long enough. Now do it
you and yours.
Put your boots on.
Make them pay in cash.
Sign the agreement and change your
family's life forever.
What father wouldn't want that?
Then your thumbprint.
Press the box.
Welcome to the running man.
This is exciting.
Ah, there you are.
I assume you two had an understanding
based on her line of work?
He's a waitress at a club.
I've got a nerve.
My apologies.
To mutually profitable collaboration.
I'm Agent Duck.
your family alliance liaison family
alliance is the network's premium
security service it's included in your
contract no point winning all that jack
just to get your people robbed and
killed we'll relocate the fam put them
an assumed name that's the one thing you
won't have to worry about you
have one call to the wife let her know
we'll be there in the morning I need to
bring her this tonight. I promise I will
be back before the show starts. No one
comes back.
I got a lock you in a really nice
apartment.
Come on, man.
I had a sick kid.
I'll deliver it now and bring back her,
I see.
Can you give her this, too?
You okay?
Where are you?
I'm at the network building. I'm fine.
Look, a man named Doug, he's gonna bring
you 500 new in cash.
Take her to Uptown Mercy, all right?
It's 24 -7. Get her a real doc, whatever
she needs.
Hey, Matt.
What did you do?
I'm on the running, man.
Listen to me.
I promise I'll be back.
I told you to never, ever wear my shoes.
Ever. Your feet smell like dead mice.
Now I have to bring them. You're an
person. What is going on here?
Mom, she stole my shoes.
Because Alyssa put them in my shoe
cubby. Take off my shoes.
Are you serious?
to starting gun fires tonight at 8.
Showtime.
Let's roll.
Rest.
As you're running back, you're going to
use it for timers, reminders, and
rewards.
Good luck on that.
You got one job out there say what's on
your mind
you're feeling angry and violent to
grieve don't think before you speak
for pussies go off curse shake your dick
at the crowd. It's all good free me
Bobby T
Daniel, you son of a bitch. How many
times I gotta tell you, do not put blue
in my amuse -bouche.
When I pull a mercury poisoning on a
show night, your bouche will not be
Dan. Oh, is this the one?
Yep.
Oh.
I know it's weird to see me in real
life, but you're used to it.
I'm flesh and blood just like you are.
My robot puts my pants on one leg at a
time.
Classic Bobby.
Not.
Shake your dick at the crowd. That's a
bad note.
Let's wait.
20 seconds, people.
All right. See you out there.
There it is.
The new Coliseum.
America.
The greatest country in the fucking
universe. We work hard. And after a long
of busting ass, we get to kick back and
feel good.
But some don't want to work for that
privilege.
These fraudsters, freeloaders.
And why should they when they can take
it from you?
Welcome to the game where we give three
of these tough guys all the freedom they
want.
Biodata Curates.
No standards, no trackers. For 30 days,
all that stands between these men and
millions is you.
Record, record, reward.
With over 10 million new dollars in
prizes won, the best audience in the
remains undefeated.
It's the running...
Your fury at the injustice of the world
has stopped you from reaching your full
potential, but now that anger is your
superpower.
Embrace it. Our program hails from right
here in Co -op City.
Ben Richards, a healthy...
35 -year -old man who thinks he's too
good to work for a living.
Mr. Rizzo's last job was a full -time
position at DefenseNet until he spilled
military secrets to Commie Union he's
not even in.
That's bullshit!
Come on, show this kid. Chill out.
That's right!
He bit the hand that feeds him because
that's what dogs do.
Remember that face?
You win 3 ,000 new dollars.
Ten thousand. It leads to a kill.
We double the prizes for the last one of
the season. Because when the stakes go
up. The stakes go down. And the stakes
beat high.
Because the thousands he wins.
Goes to his wife Sheila.
A night witch.
Who only takes the biggest tips. At the
liberty.
If you compare them. By any window.
Richard, it's up to her now to raise the
tragic kin of their sin.
What's that?
I think it's time for... Well, Mr.
Richards.
Come on, can we hear it?
Do you have any famous last words?
Yeah.
Fuck you, Dan!
Mr. Richards is what they used to refer
to as a game changer.
Now listen, I shouldn't say this, but
when the run begins, lay low with your
kind. You'll last longer.
And also, in case you missed it in your
contract, every goon you kill wins you a
10K bonus.
And it's a hundo per hunter.
I don't know how you... But I'm gonna
fuck you up someday.
That's the spirit.
Runners get a $1 ,000 new dollar advance
and a 12 -hour running start.
The hunters don't hunt until the record
and report app goes live.
Tomorrow morning. Roll to the running
game. You must take 10 minutes of on
ham per day.
These envelopes cannot be tracked.
Drop them in a network drone express
mailbox before midnight or you'll be
disqualified. Thank you. From further
winnings, but still hunted for 30 days.
Don't die for free.
Get your takes in. Roll free.
Run far.
Get rich.
Make it to midnight tomorrow and win 5
,000 new dollars. Awards increase by 1
,000 per day and double at the end of
each week. The grand prize for surviving
day 30 is now a billion new dollars.
They may be amongst you right now!
And on the left, the ghost haunting
every runner's dreams, Chief McCall!
Search and destroy, gentlemen.
Let him go!
Take a last look at these thugs.
Observe the typical disguises their kind
use to escape justice.
In mere moments, they will walk among
you.
whatever they want until we stop them
together.
13th at Obama. Hey, Running Man!
I was watching you on the freebie. 13th
at Obama.
Okay.
What's up, man?
Hey, take a pic with me. Okay.
What do you mean? No, it's okay.
You got to be nice, man, so people don't
report you.
People will do that. Not me, though,
man. I'm a nice guy. You know what?
right. Hey, we should pull over and pick
up one of these hookers. She can take
the pick, huh?
Sickest idea ever, man.
What? You don't see me on the hatch?
I saw you two blocks away on the
infrared.
What do you want?
Look, I need two ID cards and a gun.
Forget it. I don't do guns.
Go see Mickey on the third.
What in the hell is the problem?
The running man?
What were you thinking?
I had you pegged for smart. Look, I
didn't have a choice. Kathy was... Do
know how much danger you put me in
coming here?
If you want to kill yourself, fine, but
leave me out of it. Okay?
You got it?
God damn it, Ben.
IDs are 100.
It's 30 each for costumes and
accessories. I've got a priest, I've got
veteran, I've got an exec. And the rush
order makes it 200 new, all in.
Go hide out in survival.
It's aisle five.
I'm going to lock the incinerator. Oh, I
already did.
You don't mind if I check, do you?
Listen to him. If he lets go, we're all
dead. Is that a lot of these?
No, I can't keep them in stock.
Those TVs?
don't watch your back come on
so it's gonna work
absolutely okay you ready one two three
all right let's uh test out those
contacts
okay can you read anything on that shelf
E -F -E -20. Holy shit. How do you have
black Irish?
That's not for sale. Yeah, like I put
that shit in my pocket.
Only took a couple grams to blow up fat
birds in the sewers uptown.
E -F -E.
Big fucking explosion.
So, what's the plan?
I don't know.
Play low with my own kind?
Your own kind will sell you out in a
heartbeat.
I find the busiest place you can.
Just appear in the crowd. That's my
advice.
Well, you can leave the thing where you
came.
Molly, I had to do it.
No, you didn't.
I was going to bring you on here.
Sort of as a partner. I should have told
Sheila yesterday.
But I wanted to tell you myself.
Hey, too late for that now.
Well, Godspeed.
See you on the big screen.
New York City, one way.
They've traveled,
Mr. Springer.
He nicked your face.
Did you ever saw it? You say anything, I
will kill you so fast your mom won't
even wake up. But your mustache.
So sorry about that.
I'm going to snap back.
Now arriving at the offense station,
this is the final stop on this train.
Welcome to the Brandt Hotel, Mr.
Springer.
You shaved your mustache.
Fell off on the train.
I hate when that happens.
Everything okay, Mr. Springer?
Yeah.
Just, uh... Have a good night.
Day. You know what?
Apple.
say i have to be on camera 10 minutes a
day they didn't say which part so
guess you can watch my ass take a nap
One down.
Rewind.
Live update!
Let's go!
See,
watch the running, man.
I guess.
I heard there's this guy on there who
kind of looks like me and he's really
or something. I don't know.
I don't know.
I'm going to come back in a little bit
and I'm going to try to ask you that
again.
And that's Jansky stepping out with
his... The fuse
and bullet.
It's just a matter of time.
Get out of there, buddy.
Better eat up, Tim.
Enjoy those last bites before it's last
rites. Move, move. You're walking. It's
the fucking running man.
Here we go.
Oh, man.
Hi,
I'd like to extend my stay for three
days.
I'd be happy to arrange that for you,
Mr. Springer.
In the same room, if possible.
Let me see what I can do.
Thank you.
You're in luck.
Looks like I can keep you in the same
room, Mr. Springer.
Great.
Can I get you a car this morning?
Uh, you know what?
I have to go walk.
Hey,
brother, I need to get off the street.
Oh, yeah?
Looking for a place to rag out for the
month.
Mm -hmm.
Or the net, if you know what I mean.
Oh, is that so?
I'll give you $100 for your room and
another $100 for your jacket.
A deuce hundo for this rat -ass jacket
and that rat -ass room?
Well, you need to get a Jamaica plane,
pick up your head, man. Come on.
Put that shit away, wouldn't you mind?
Let us kill him.
Let me see your face.
Where'd you deploy?
Alaska.
Hey, Shrapnel. You ain't seen combat,
but I reckon it ain't stolen valor if
paid me for it.
Thanks.
Hey, you listen to me. You stay out of
my stash.
I catch you in that basement again, I'm
going to stop you. And I'm going to get
Big Bird to take care of you. He'll kick
your cow ass over the moon. Beat it.
Good luck with that.
You know, I've always been the guy who
fought first.
I showed up to work first, I left last.
Hasn't done much for me, obviously.
I mean, I'm on the murder show.
What are you going to do?
Take on the whole world?
Sweet. So here I am, a grown -ass man
playing hide -and -seek for money.
Keep it cool.
Try not to burn out.
Depraved. Demonic.
Deceased.
What's happening for the remaining
winner's week?
Tune in and find out.
Next up, rich and bold, it's those
Americanos.
Hey, Jim.
How do you like this energy wine?
I'm a big fan.
Love it.
How about you, Bill?
That's pretty much my favorite thing,
Jim.
So, uh, guys, you mind if I ask you a
personal question?
Why do we all have the same voice?
Relax, Ben.
We'll know later.
Good to see you too, Frank.
You better rest Frank.
At least you got someone to talk to.
We're dead, Frank.
There's no way out.
Never.
I don't believe they've located the room
this mother's hiding in.
Walk the walk.
Down there.
What's this?
McComb's giving the signal.
The rover can't.
This is why we play the game running
fans.
The moment of truth.
Where these animals find out we're in a
society of rules.
And there they are.
The hunters posted on our side of the
juice room. We're going in.
Here we go.
Not going anywhere.
Bravo.
Hey, buddy.
Get out pretty deep. The hunters are
racing to intercept their prey.
Run, Mr. Richards!
This is what we want, running man!
Let's go, go!
Stop filming me!
No, he's out.
He's headed for the lot.
Let me stop.
Richards, you're going down.
I'm still here.
Just kidding.
Everyone's looking for you.
Ayo, stay here. I'll be right back.
I got you, Regis.
Don't run around and survive the love
update. How the hell are you?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I can pay you.
Just get me off the street for the
night.
Hell no.
Bob and Dee. What?
We need street meds.
My sister got cancer real bad.
Make it 10.
Get her the good stuff.
Not bad.
I love the price of you.
How fast can you move on, Richard?
Faster every day.
Just a shocking amount of destruction
here. The NCG on tactical alert as units
pour in from neighboring districts,
seeking justice for their fallen
The NCG bomb squad is on scene combing
through the rubble for evidence.
Preliminary reports indicate Richard set
off the explosion in the basement.
His body is yet to be found.
Baby.
You can set your grandkids up for life
with a home recording report.
Do you think the network would rather
pay us reward money or make up some
bullshit and arrest us?
What if I gave you enough to get your
sister real forms?
Say 500 new.
I can get you out of varsity, but it
won't be for money.
Bro, this dude ain't going nowhere.
Goons got the hoots around it. We out.
Stop.
Just a little pinch and you can't feel
good, bro.
Richard's letter.
Find out tomorrow night. I'm a running
man, baby.
You know, you seem like a smart cat.
What made you sign up to be a cog in
that propaganda machine?
I'm just trying to take care of my
family.
Just like you and your sister.
Jim.
My kid was sick.
I sent my wife enough to get her well.
Now I'm trying to win enough to get them
out.
She's only two.
So if I do my job, she'll never even
remember Slumside.
Okay, Richards.
I can get you past that blockade.
But I'm gonna need a couple days to set
it up, so hide out here in the meantime.
You know, you could go to full 30 if you
play smart.
And what makes you such an expert?
Tune in and find out.
Until the cold day.
I don't want a lot, I want just enough.
So why is it got to be so damn tough?
What goes on behind the scenes of the
biggest freebie show of all time?
to The Apostle, episode 30, The Real
Rules of the Running Man. It's your day
do and distribute.
The network has three types for every
run. Oh my God.
Type 1, hopeless dude.
Hopeless dude is cursed with a fatal
misunderstanding of human nature. Tim?
Yeah? He usually lasts less than 48
hours.
Come and get me.
Dinner's served, pal.
Oh, damn.
Oh, he is cooked.
Type 2. Negative dude.
Negative dude knows he ain't got a
chance in hell. He just wants to go out
a bang or two. Make life greater.
Leave a fucking crater.
Bro gets smoked by the end of week one
because he buys too much ass and not
enough food with his running start.
Slave to his appetite, he often serves
himself up on a plate. Ha!
Suck this in hell!
Boom!
Run it out!
Type three.
Oh, yeah!
Final dude. Final dude. has a fierce
will to survive yet he never wins the
network they can't find anyone any time
but if a runner's getting good ratings
they let him run 13 days and just like
papa always said you can cry but you
can't catch a ghost so by the end of
week two radios usually peak oh shit the
crowd wants blood and final dude becomes
a victim they might hide from
is that supposed to inspire me oh come
on man don't you get it after that
tonight live prime time you you are
final dude
and they're gonna squeeze every last
drop of ratings out of your ass so you
at least until Negative Dude flames out
to get somewhere safe, which gives us
enough time to set you up for the
biggest underdog win in game show
So where the hell is safe?
I'm working on it.
Hey, Penbell.
It's been a while.
So you know what you're doing?
Guess we'll find out. Got a package
headed your way.
Yeah, special delivery, as seen on
preview.
Okay, I see you.
And pick up location B. Right.
Mama's coming, baby.
Okay, okay.
So how does a five
-year -old get lung cancer?
Radioactive dust.
From the Rhode Island explosion.
Never heard about that.
Yeah, you never heard of it because the
network owns the news.
Just like they own that munitions
factory. Just like they own the
why bother complying with safety regs,
right?
That's how Joan got sick.
For all you watching, not the execs.
Not the technicos.
You live in a tower uptown. I'm not
talking to you.
I'm talking to the people in the co -op.
The ones who can't get a job. The
squatter tribe.
The kids are getting shot for looking at
a goo in the wrong way.
There's something you all need to know.
The network is giving our kids cancer
and they are covering it up.
Previously on The Running Man.
I'm still here.
Just sit, eaters.
Uh -oh.
Not the execs. Not the technicals. If
you live in a tower of town, I'm not
talking to you. I'm talking to the
people in the car.
The squatter tribe.
The ones who can't get a job.
The kids getting shot for looking at a
goon the wrong way. There's something
all need to know.
I laughed my ass off smoking those
goons. And I wasn't just laughing at the
screams. I was laughing at their kids.
Now you know how it felt when daddy did
it to someone else.
I didn't say that. Okay, I made a video
about the network giving kids cancer.
It's all fake.
Son, you gotta get him out of here.
Tonight. Right now. I want him gone.
Bring him home.
What kind of world are we living in?
Running fans, I just heard from producer
Dan Kelly, who has personally doubled
the reward for Ben Richards.
Now, $20 ,000 is deducted for any
concerns or corporate reports that lead
stab. Mark, Mark.
Well, it's getting crazy on you. Yeah,
the game's around tonight.
Yeah, we gotta roll. You ready?
Go.
Okay. Keep your eye on those.
Those biker boys are on the valley. I'm
going to reward them. Got it.
Look, they're following us. I know, I
know. Stay cool.
Come on.
Yo what's going on?
My pen pal needs a day to prep transport
to a shelter.
You can trust him with your life.
Just don't mention hot dogs around the
man.
Say hot dog?
Yep. Go catch that flow train to Maine.
Less people in the sticks, but keep your
head down and don't trust anyone.
This guy.
Name's Elton. Hardcore.
Down for the course.
You really think this will work?
Look, we know they track denominators.
And pre -shoot the rest of your self
-tapes. My man heads out, drives them on
the way. Why are you safe underground?
They won't know what hit them.
Out.
That's what you got.
Just in case.
Why are you helping me?
You see the power they have?
If we don't guide each other's back,
this game's over before it even begins.
What's up, America?
I was about to tell you the network
fakes these self -tapes, but if I did,
they'd just fake this one too. So, I'm
just going to read you something
Dear Diary, I woke up with the blahs
today.
My regular gig of killing heroic goons
was feeling too routine.
Time for a me day.
So I ate my favorite breakfast in bed,
defenseless puppies. I could have eaten
one.
Then I did yoga and blew up a
courthouse.
I know.
It's a good habit.
But tonight, I'm going to go out to
another school.
And then, you know,
you know, you know what you're doing.
Mr.
Richards thinks he's funny. But what if
he was the last laugh when McComb
catches them laughing?
Mr. Richards?
We're still here, you shittiers!
Damn, Richard, that's a tough act to
follow.
Yeah!
Oh!
Go off, neighbor.
Oh, my God! Look at him fall!
Who does next?
Definitely her.
Laugh, Lincoln.
Real. Cheap boys going down. No way. I
got ten claims there's Ben Richards died
next. Oh, come on. He's picked the
network off all the way. That's why he's
gonna win. The guy's got marks. Yeah,
he's one of us.
Taking on the boys in black.
Giving the world a finger.
He's your final runner.
That's a fact. Damn straight.
What do you think, Reverend?
You seen this Richards guy?
No.
But he sounds like quite the character.
What's wrong with you?
He's blind, you fucking idiot.
Me again.
Look, here's the real deal.
I'm not out here trying to fight the
power.
I'm not out here to have fun.
I'm here to win and get back to my
family.
You won't see me throwing Molotov
cocktails. You won't see me throwing
In fact, you won't see me at all.
Just in time, father.
Best take out of Maine.
Thank you.
My son.
Hey, Charlie.
Can I ask you something?
Of course, my son.
I got this girlfriend.
Okay.
Am I going to hell for using rubbers?
You may well go for an obvious number.
I've 10 brothers and sisters.
My father said he was in hell every
single day.
Thanks, Father.
Have a good night.
Careful out there.
You think you're the guy who stops you
from seeing my daughter again?
This is a message for my fellow
citizens.
And let me make this clear for the cheap
seats.
If I die on this show, I died for the
two things I believe in.
My wife and my kid, everything else and
everyone else can fuck off.
We all know it. But that
sound is... We're paying Miss Laughlin a
run for her money.
She rolled the dice on a very public
appearance at the Holy Grail Casino. But
didn't gamble that our hundreds would be
there.
Looks like some red bugs.
Sorry hunters, all you managed to kill
was my vibe.
Remember, kids, don't drink and drive.
Unless you're good at it.
That's a hot touch, kids.
Beyond the cash reward, Jeff and Gina
will receive a lifetime supply of fun
twink cereal.
And then...
Come on, hurry.
Hunters will be out for blood.
They hate civilian kills.
Things are going to start ramping up.
Well, wouldn't be surprised if they fire
up the DNA papers tonight.
Oh, what a tough guy.
I'm not looking for any friends. Don't
ask for an autograph.
Alfie! What if he's in Derry?
He's not in Derry, Mom.
Don't worry, it's fine, Mom.
She thinks you're an actual demon, but
she's fairly deaf. We can use our normal
voices. Kill him, wealthy bastard.
Hand him down!
She used to be a kind, clever woman.
This is where it all happens.
Amateur lab for making handcrafted soap,
far as you know.
Normal, non -revolutionary literature.
Wink, wink.
Copier for my harmless community
newsletter.
You follow my drift?
Uh -huh.
So what's a DNA sever?
A black -off scanner that ID highly
fragmented strands of DNA.
Things are hidden in every street lamp
across the country, which is why you've
got to get underground ASAP.
Man, if you want to ask, just ask.
What is that with the hot dog cart?
My dad was a cop.
a good cop quit in protest when the
network privatized local police he
officers should be accountable to the
towns that pay them not the government
sure as hell not the mega court so he
bought the cart busted his ass we never
missed a meal better an honorable hot
dog vendor than a crooked goon but his
friends who signed on with the ncg
didn't appreciate his choices and they
him know every chance they got He made
damn sure we were safe in the house.
And every time he took that card out,
well, you see what I did to my mom.
And this is what they did to my dad.
His buddies on the force never solved
the case. Because they're the ones who
killed him.
But you can't kill an idea.
Dad was their worst nightmare.
A free man with a conscience.
And everything they destroyed in him
lives on in me.
Like a nuclear blast.
It never burns out.
Monster.
I'm good.
Any rooms?
You can't outrun space.
And you cannot hide from destiny.
We're back going up there.
I have a detailed map for how to get
there. You can survive down there for
years, but you'll only need it for two
weeks.
I'll pre -shoot the rest of your tapes
tomorrow.
What do you think?
Um... Or... Maybe just... White.
Hardcore.
Check this out.
You could be arrested just for having
the truth in your house.
So this won't be distributed until right
after you win.
What the hell?
It's a special issue on the network's
most heinous crimes.
What does that have to do with me?
A bomb's chemicals hold great power.
But without an initiator to make it go
boom, it's harmless.
You know why they cheered for you down
there?
They think you just might win.
And if you can survive against those
goons, so can they.
The people have had it.
This country's ready to blow.
And you're the initiator. I'm not.
The initiator.
I'm a guy trying to give back to his
family.
It's you against the world either way,
brother.
Why not be both?
My mom picked the bathroom across the
hall that called in, so that's all you.
If the light in the hallway is off,
she's asleep.
Hey, I appreciate what you're doing.
But if they find out you helped me,
those same goons that got your dad,
come for you.
What can help?
The message is that Dad needs to see you
someday.
I wanted to impart a little Dad advice.
Rule one.
Take care of your mom.
She's your best friend.
Rule two,
bullies are cowards.
Hit back.
Rule three, you can be kind and strong
at the same time.
Rule four, don't trust the network.
Ever.
And rule five, you remember your dad
loves
you a whole lot.
I'll be looking out for you.
No matter what.
Ha!
I knew it was you, devil murderer!
Stay away from my elf! Ma 'am! Ma 'am!
You savage!
Wait! Mom!
You'll never eat puppies again!
Mom, no!
Mom! It's okay! He's a friend! Help me!
No!
Ma 'am! Ma 'am!
If you press that button...
The NCG will come and fire me. Okay,
they will not care who gets caught in
crossfire. It will be a bloodbath.
We don't need everybody going to the
state coming through that door, right?
Don't.
Network community guard, what crime
would you like to report?
Ben Richards just broke into my home.
Okay, stay where you are. I saw you.
We gotta get going.
I just need five minutes of fun with
these guys before we do.
What? Grab your stuff. I'll get the
scenes.
They're not listening. It's dangerous.
Tom, get in the safe room. No, I didn't
want to see you die.
You hear that, Will? You're gonna die.
There.
Oh, yes, we do.
Fastest the hunters ever arrived on
scene in four minutes, 30 seconds.
We'll be long gone by that.
Hey,
big boy.
You brought us up here so you could fly
down a pole? I brought us up here so we
could fly down a pole!
See?
Four minutes flat.
Told you we'd be long gone. Long gone?
We are still in the goddamn house!
Not for long!
flashlight. Pretty powerful.
Yeah.
Come on.
I'm going to separate your Achilles and
drag you outside.
She wants to end your run in person.
On camera.
Gilligan, people are dying, you fucking
psychopath.
If you can fake everything, why don't
you just fake the whole show?
Believe me, we have tried. But humans
bring that special, unpredictable spark.
The audience lives for these happy
accidents.
A little advice?
I'll pass.
Make sure my family gets the money.
Richards, don't go.
You can still win this game, but you
have to play it smart.
I just sent a rover into that tunnel.
You want me to offer one of your own
guys?
It's all good for me.
I can slow them down.
Take back roads to the shelter.
Survival is the win.
This way.
Take this map.
That bunker is in the middle of the
forest.
Remember, Richards, you're the
initiator.
Bright red blood pumps adrenaline
through your veins.
This game is no game.
Life and death are on the line.
Can you feel it, Mr. Richards?
Congratulations.
You took out a hunter.
Now it's down to four of them.
Plus, every citizen of this great
nation.
One in five pieces with the big rock.
Bunkers dug into the hill.
smell it the acorns think of fear as the
prey animal realizes he's surrounded
by predators reality sinks in as he
scurries to hide desperately hoping to
survive but deep down he already knows
it's too late because this is
america god damn it and we don't pull up
with no bullshit what must is our
birthright set it free
Richard shows this path, and it's up to
you to show him where it ends.
Keep your eyes open so you can see the
terror in his, and hunt him down!
This shall never come.
This is a method for killing.
A dead
I'm starting to get how this game works.
It's not about me winning or losing.
It's about your ratings.
About how much chaos I can cause.
I'm taking this thing all the way to the
end.
And I'm done playing.
So here's the deal.
I will see my family again.
And as long as they keep getting paid,
you can put whoever you want.
in front of me i will run through all of
them i know you fight dirty
or guess what you son of a i'm from
slumside let's throw the rule book out
here's the mutually profitable
annihilation you want to go i'll give
Let's do this.
We interrupt the Americanos for a live
update from the running man. We don't
like this show. The floor is done.
We're the only ones tense enough to
think it's real. I know. It's so funny.
Please stay still.
Is that the U .K.? Please.
Go, go. Get on fire.
Drive! Take the next back road north. I
can't. My power's on empty. Your battery
is 93 % charged.
Those goons are going to frag us if you
don't back this car up.
Right now!
Your car is dead.
People need self -driving cars.
Recalculating.
Keep it pointed north.
All the way to the border.
Go ahead.
Say what you gotta say.
Why?
So you can go crazy and kill me?
No.
You have one minute to speak freely.
How do you live with yourself?
You dare sit there and criticize my
driving?
Tell me how to operate my own car?
I am a member of society.
You disgust me.
You abandoned that starving baby, that
horrible wife of yours.
You can what?
Kill people for money?
And you only kill the best people.
The people who protect us from wealth
like you.
And that's not a word I use.
That is my family.
A number finally came up for the part.
Watched Kathy try ice cream for the
first time.
That was the best day of my life.
So yeah, you're right.
The show is so fake.
Not the bullets.
Not the death.
Just the part that makes people like you
think you're better than people like
us. Let me ask you something. How much
was that scarf?
Huh? More than the meds my daughter
needed when she was dying of the flu?
The flu!
That is a human life hanging around your
neck.
You seem to be doing fine.
Who can blame you? It's a nice scarf.
I'm not a bad person.
No, do not start crying.
I will shoot us both if you start
crying.
Cry when it's over.
When will that be?
Yielding for an emergency vehicle.
Nice. Disable it. Disable it. Do not
pull. I don't know how. Yielding in 150
feet.
50 feet.
In 20 feet.
You have successfully yielded. Nice.
We're here securing our homestead in the
name of the network.
Don't worry, lady. We're the good guys.
Just step out of the car.
You'll be safe with us.
It's him we want.
The producers just killed an hour ago,
Chef.
Except me.
I don't do that.
Those men were just trying to protect me
from you.
What is it going to take for you to
get... I am not the bad guy!
Take the car.
Drive away. I don't want to hurt you.
You think they're going to let you walk
after seeing that? You're on the show
now.
No, I'm not!
Rickards lives.
And this time, he's got a hostage.
Amelia Williams, a 27 -year -old realtor
from Bangor, Maine.
Help me!
He's got a gun!
Welcome to the Running Man.
Help me! The crisis continues as Ms.
Williams' gray Alpine heads north on
Rock Siding Road. The hostage situation
has triggered the NCT to go into full
tactical alert.
Help me!
Turn it off. He's got a gun!
Just turn it off!
Unbelievable. Yeah, it's a circus, all
right. So they're just going to keep
filming us?
If a runner gets good ratings, they let
him run.
Oh, God.
Is that a blocking?
All right.
We'll play our parts, then let us pass.
That's it.
Keep driving.
We're not going to shoot.
How do you know?
Because they're going to wait for the
show to start.
I'm alive.
To what life?
Kill me.
Why did he turn for you when I'm a
hostage?
Unbelievable.
Amelia, can you give me the gun?
Why not?
You're obviously the hero.
I don't think we're going to need this
anymore.
Oh,
my God. I just saw Ben Richards.
I'm sorry. Wait. I am Ben Richards.
And if you don't want to be the reason
Amelia dies, get this message to
Do what he says, please.
You heard the lady.
make up some bullshit when it had to be
done.
Look at all these people who know the
truth.
Are you willing to kill all of them?
Because I am.
I'm holding on to this bullhorn with my
right hand.
My left hand is in my front couch,
wrapped around 12 pounds of black Irish.
When I used to work at Network Public
Utility,
You get these two -ton fatberg, take
less than a gram to blow those up.
12 pounds.
I'll vaporize everything in a half -mile
radius.
Oh, shit.
BFB -20 is the most highly regulated
industrial explosive. We haven't even
foot in a state that does that.
Guess Molly didn't tell you everything.
I got my finger stuck in the detonator
ring.
And it's on half cock.
So, I want one of those big, fancy,
flying V airplanes.
I want two auto -shoots handed to Amelia
at the bottom of the ramp.
If the future's out, Todd, do you make
any sudden moves?
If you don't back those trucks up and
let me on that tarmac right fucking now,
you won't even hear it go boom.
I'll just see you in hell and laugh in
your face.
You got one minute.
Shouldn't take long.
He's got a direct line to the boss.
Last chance to run.
No.
You made me feel like I'm the bad guy.
Now I have to prove I'm not.
Why don't you show what I think?
You're not the one I'm trying to prove
it to.
Who wants our plan?
I'm going to convince them your handbag
is a bomb long enough to bail out over
Canada.
They'll never let me win, so I'm going
to slip out the back door and wait out
the clock.
We just have to keep the audience
entertained until they cross the border.
What if they call your bluff?
You make sure they know it's real. Get
scared, freak out, curse, scream, call
the worst names possible.
Just remember, everything bad...
It's all good freebie.
Act terrified when McConey hands you the
chutes. I won't have to act.
If he grabs his gun, you'll know it's
time to go off.
So, you think you're the guy who stops
me from seeing my daughter again?
So start today.
Get on the plane.
only if you take your mask off audience
will love it keep dreaming
We'll start today.
Welcome aboard, Mr. Richards, to the
Metair Flying V Luxury Jetliner, the
ultimate in private travel.
With state -of -the -art safety
features, this is first -class comfort
-high. So sit back and enjoy the most
relaxing flight of your life.
Welcome aboard, Mr. Richards.
I'm Captain Holloway.
You'll excuse me if I don't shake your
hand.
That's First Officer Dunninger and
Navigation Officer Donahue to your left.
Looks like you're missing one.
Hey, Captain. How many lavatories are on
this rust bucket?
Four. Six.
Why don't you check them all for
stowaways?
Anyone sneaks up on me, it's gonna be a
real short ride.
So where are we headed tonight?
Plot a route over the richest homes from
here to Canada.
Fly as low as you can. Let me know when
we're 10 minutes from the border.
As you wish.
Hey, Richard.
Six minutes to showtime.
You should get that last meal before
they clear me to blow your head off in
front of a couple billion people.
Oh, yeah?
You know, you could really put some
makeup on before the show starts.
Fuck the show!
Let's go.
Oh, you want to go?
We can all go right now! Just stop!
Do it! Do it, tough guy! Why are you
doing this?
See my twitch. Show him the bomb!
Show it to him before he shoots you and
kills us all!
Don't show it!
Because I don't want to feel like this
anymore!
Do you fucking hear me? I'm done!
I'm done!
Richard, what if I offer you an amnesty
deal and an exit visa?
You're nothing but a Halloween costume.
You can't offer me shit.
You're true, Mr. Richards.
You can, but I can't. How about I offer
you a deal?
You tell your hunters in the cockpit to
do what I tell them, otherwise I blow up
this shit and everyone on it!
Dan, I admire your commitment to the
bet, but we're short on time, so...
I'll be blunt.
We know you're bluffing.
Flying V Mark II has scanners built into
the doors.
It's been wildly entertaining.
But you can give Amelia her lovely
handbag back now.
Evan?
Evan? Don't.
That's game.
Safe to that weapon, sir. Evan, are you
insane?
The show hasn't even started. Hand over
your gun and go to the back of the jet.
Thank you.
You can remain there until I say
otherwise.
I need a moment to have a word with Mr.
Richards to discuss a sensitive matter.
Let's keep this between us.
It wasn't too long ago that someone with
my job thought it was more important to
force some hypocritical moral message
down society's throat than to simply
entertain them.
They forgot about the power of illusion,
the power of the star, which is what
you are, Richards.
And this is why we want to offer you
your own show.
Now picture it.
A former runner, redeemed through
righteous vengeance, turns his life
become a lethal force for good.
They call him the Hunter.
The board has authorized me to pay you
five million new dollars per season.
There's only one condition.
Sit back, watch the intro, and we're
bobbing you to kill every Hunter on that
jet.
Conditions met, I'll remote pilot you
back to the studio jet port where the
President of the United States will
induct you as Hunter number six.
Another title idea I'm playing with.
The data says the revenge plot. Revenge.
Revenge for what?
Who is going to root for a guy who kills
your national heroes?
I call bullshit, Dan.
Let me worry about the creative.
No deal.
The truth, then.
Revenge for your wife and child.
Why would I ever believe you?
Because.
If they were still alive, I'd hold them
at gunpoint and force you to do whatever
I want.
You torture them right in front of you.
I didn't want to show you this, but I'm
out of time to save your life.
The hunter you killed was part of a
tight crew.
McCone and the men in that cockpit flew
to Co -op City to Sheila and Kathy's
secret uptown location.
They badged their way past the family
alliance agents.
I'm sorry, Ben.
Not all accidents are happy.
The audience is already on your side.
Once I show them footage of McCone and
his men killing your family, they will
follow you into hell.
Think of what this does for your
narrative.
30 seconds to showtime, Ben.
You'll find a gun by the coffee station
in the galley. But if you don't sign
before the theme music ends, I'll order
the bastards that killed your family to
kill you too.
Tune in and find out.
Everyone, everyone, please help.
Help, help.
Running Man.
We start today's episode with a heavy
heart.
We here at The Running Man believe in
following the rules.
So it pains me to tell you that one of
our most important rules...
has been broken by the very men we
entrust to enforce them.
Chief McCollum and his hunters.
And that rule is, we protect the
Runner's family from harm.
No one would believe we didn't.
We thought it only fair to let Richards
administer the penalty for this grave
infraction.
As we go along, it's Richard's.
Hey, Richards.
You're making coffee?
Yeah.
How do you... Take it!
I'm sitting alone.
I'm sitting
alone.
And then, there was one.
Three hunters down, but the deadliest
among them is still somewhere on this
He took the other parachute. I couldn't
stop him.
Strap that on.
keep your head down the prey has become
the predator
It all comes down to this.
You
want
to know who's stopping you from beating
your kid again?
This is how they fire me, what do you
think they'll do to you?
You think you're the only runner ever
got offered a deal?
You think surviving two weeks in pain
makes you big shit?
Try 29 days.
What's more likely?
A. I killed your family.
B. Killian sold you just the right lie
to get a bloodbath season finale.
Or C.
You're too fucking stupid to figure it
out.
Take it from someone who took the deal
to be a hunter instead of the hunted.
The only time you'll ever see your
family again is when they torture them
front of you.
Fuck with your head enough to make you
want to kill it all away.
You're full of shit.
You're all full of shit.
Truth is, I'm doing you a favor.
Hey, Gillian!
You think I needed time to waste, this
loser?
You outran fate!
That's game.
Can I borrow your scarf?
Let's take him back on the ground.
This shoe should open on its own.
But if it doesn't, just let her rip.
When you get on the ground, just run
like hell. Go with that.
When I tell you, you're going to pull
that down all the way.
I'm sorry they did this to you.
I did it to myself.
Not this.
Ben Richards, you are the man.
We have commanded the jet.
Best trauma surgeons are already on the
tarmac, ready to patch you up as good as
new. But wait.
Making his freebie debut with a special
message.
The creator of Running Man, super
producer Dan Killian.
Mr. Richards, we here at the network
believe you embody the raw strength.
strength, and salt of the earth moral
backbone this country stands for. And we
want, no, we need to see more.
This summer, Ben Richards is 106.
Congratulations, Ben, and welcome to the
network family.
I already got a family.
Did you kill him or not, Dan?
Give it up for Dan Killian.
times do you get to tell 2 billion
people how you really feel?
How does it feel to be a hero, Ben?
Nothing I've done on the show makes me a
hero.
I tried to be a hero once.
I've been blacklisted in my ass.
My daughter got sick.
This is the only job I could get.
Seems like the whole point of freebie is
to make us hate each other so
they can keep stealing from us.
When we fight in the mud, you want the
truth.
Turn it off.
We are all being fucked by the network.
Find out who really runs it.
Record. Report them.
Get their names.
You just met one of them.
Dan Killian.
You remember that face.
Don't watch for me.
Watch who pays for it.
Turn it off.
Great speech.
Too bad I'm the only one who saw it.
We've been on an ad break since you said
nothing you did on the show made you a
hero. You think it was worth it? You
think your little rant made you a
We're going live again in 30.
This time you'll play your part, because
if not, I'm gonna run this instead.
I told you I was gonna burn this
building down and everyone in it!
That was fast.
Work with me, Richards.
Don't throw your life away.
Don't make me fly that jet into the
network building.
They'll blow you out of the sky.
Are they dead or alive, Dan?
Who? My family. Who cares? If I told you
they were alive, would you even believe
me? We are alive in five, four, three,
two, one.
Now, okay, have it your way.
I told you I was gonna burn this
building!
Are you insane?
There's 5 ,000 innocent people in this
building!
Look
at what
you've done.
Are you happy?
I told you I was gonna fuck you up.
Yeah.
The main column, everyone!
The NCT will blow him out of the sky!
true believers let's wind that back beth
richards
legend the network wants you to think
that on day 18 of his run after taking
all five hunters the longest surviving
contestants in season one committed
suicide by surface to air missile The
apostle calls bullshit. First of all,
cut the ad six minutes earlier than
usual and ran them for twice as long.
must have needed the time to write this
fake ass shit.
I will sit you in hell and laugh in your
face.
And then they swamped the crowd.
Where did Purple Shirt Guy come from?
Season 5, episode 13 to be exact.
That's how dumb the network thinks we
are. Their biodistortions meant none of
knew the truth about what happened on
that jet until a revolutionary riot girl
found the jet's black box on the roof of
her co -op. Her uncle had the audio
duped, distributed, and put it on blast.
Turn it off.
And God damn it, did we ever.
The network wasn't about to give us the
gospel, so we learned how to give it to
each other. Ben let the fuse, and the
truth exploded like a newly applied
the network even knew it existed.
Don't watch freebie.
Watch who pays for it.
But questions remain about that fateful
night.
Keep going, kid! Did the hunters really
assassinate Ben's family?
Did Killian sell him just the right lie
for a bloodbath season finale? And the
big one on everyone's mind.
Did Ben survive?
The Apostles' research reveals that one
of the flying V Mark II state -of -the
-art safety features was a crew escape
pod just about the size of this so
-called debris.
Did Ben cheat death one last time? Stop
filming me! The network won't say, but
one thing's for sure.
He's still here, you shit -eaters.
These are adorable.
Oh, no, sorry, those aren't mine.
The guy outside bought them for you,
Mrs. Richards.
Groceries, too.
You were indeed a tough actor.
Where do you think you're going?
You don't hear that?
I'd say that's some valuable audience
feedback, Dan. No, no, no. You get back
out there and you do your job. How about
you do my job?
Hey, I've been crushing the ratings for
20 years. I own that audience. You don't
think I can turn this around?
You're the one who wanted to make him a
star, Dan.
Mission accomplished.
It's his show now.
You think he could just walk?
Sweeties. Please, take another look at
my contract.
Page 42, paragraph 6. There's a special
clause in the smallest effect that
reads, Fuck you.
Ten seconds?
Ten seconds, Dan.
Coco, come on, let's go.
You know what?
Fuck that.
This is my house. I set the rules.
Max and Steve, drown them out. Sir, are
you sure this is like the thing right
now?
And action.