Foreign Language Only Subs. No English Subs. by mykaat
En Sabah Nur.
Now you will rule for eternity, my lord.
Sleep.
Let the transference begin.
Death to the false god.
Protect him!
Yeah!
Ten ﬁghts waged.
Ten ﬁghts won.
The Winged Warrior.
The Bird of Prey.
The Angel of Death.
ANGEL!
Yeah!
Let's hear it for the fat man!
Our next challenger...
comes straight...
from the Munich Circus.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the only one that could take on an Angel...
is the Devil himself.
I give you...
the amazing...
the fantastic...
NIGHTCRAWLER!
Caution
High voltage!
Sorry mutants!
Hey.
Did you get lost little mouse?
The ﬁght is over there.
And it's about to get exciting.
Ah, you mean this?
Nightcrawler!
Nightcrawler! Nightcrawler!
They went that way!
Have a good night, Henryk.
You too, Milosz.
Me.
Do you sell rugs?
You're not allowed in this area.
This rug is for sale?
I said, this...
Earthquake!
l gotta get out of here.
Give them a report.
Something happened here.
l can tell them it's real.
Nina!
Nina.
Are you alright?
She's ﬁne.
Then let her go!
We will.
We just wanted to have a word
You’re not wearing your badges.
No metal.
Some guys at the factory said
they saw something today.
Something that didn’t add up.
Put your weapons away.
You've been a good citizen, Henryk...
A good neighbor... a good worker.
I want to believe that's who you are.
It is.
But nobody in this town really knows you.
Yes you do.
I am Henryk Gurzsky.
Jakob, I've had dinner in your home...
And you were lying the whole time.
I brought a killer into my house.
ls this you?
Are you the one they call Magneto?
Take me in.
Please...
Just let my daughter go.
Go with your mother.
Please.!
Don't leave me.
I'm not going to let them take you.
Nina.
What's going on?
She’s one of them?
Tell her to stop!
She can’t control it!
She’s scared of you!
I'm not going to let them take you!
Make her stop!
Nina! Nina!
Nina.
Nina, Nina. no...
No, please. Please!
Please.
Not my babies.
You know what we do to thieves.
Pick a hand.
Enough.
If you're with her, I suggest you walk away.
While you still can.
Walk away
Who rules this world?
What language is that?
Clown-face. What's the deal?
Beat it!
I'm sorry.
You can't feel it, can you?
Now you feel it.
So you really haven't seen her
in all these years"
l must say, Apollo...
the way you ape human behavior
is remarkable.
I am Apollo.
I've never seen another
mutant in this town.
You speak Egyptian?
Arabic?
English?
l'm a scientist.
My particular specialty...
Great ﬁghter.
She’s my hero.
I want to be like her.
There's some food here. Not much.
I don't believe it.
You love me.
Love you?
Illogical.
I'm not some simple shepherdess
you can awe.
Why, I could no more love you...
than I could love a new species
of bacteria
What are you doing?
Learning.
Cleansed.
Aphrodite.
You were right.
Yes.
The time is past.
There is no room for gods.
.
Caliban knows it.
Mystique.
.
Some of you spoke to the police...
about what you believe
you witnessed here yesterday.
You want to know my powers...
know who I am...
see what I can do?
I'll show you.
Think of the person you love most
in your life.
Your wife.
Mother.
Daughter.
Now that person will know what it is
to lose someone they love.
And live with that pain.
Forever.
Henryk, please.
Don't do this.
My name isn’t Henryk.
My name is Magneto.
I can't!
Our dear Father...
hold me in the light of God.
Hold me in the light of God.
Protect me from danger.
Save me by Your command.
Listen to my prayer.
And keep me safe.
A better world.
...all of your towers and temples...
Will fall.
And the dawn of a new age will rise.
Logan.